on the cyber fiscal system.
Yeah, so yeah, I don't know if that's enough for you
or you want me to do.
(laughing)
It's okay, I think we can table that for another time.
Yeah, that's it.
Who wants to go next?
Would you like to go ahead, Garett?
Yeah, yeah, I can go ahead, yeah.
So my name is Garett.
I'm actually now living in Germany, so near Frankfurt.
So it's kind of midnight, so I just woke up.
So it's like 3 a.m. in the morning now.
I work as a AI engineer in a company already for a while
before I studied master in computer science,
focused in AI.
And my work is now mainly focusing on multi-agent system
that to build some productive AI or agent AI system
for the company.
So basically, for research part, I did relatively less.
I mostly attend the online courses like this Berkeley MOC,
and then also from my job, a little bit research.
But mainly, I, yeah, so learn AI from work
and also like, yeah, by myself, so yeah.
Sorry if I may add a few things which might be helpful.
Being part of the team.
Yeah, so I am a bit behind with AI
after not doing something for almost two years now.
And I mostly do research now.
So why I joined the hackathon is because
I would love to do an internship
and I need to do some dirty
works with some coding and stuff.
Yeah, I've never done a hackathon before.
It's a dream experience.
Yeah, I could have out.
Yeah, I mean, for me, it's kind of similar.
I mean, not really looking kind for a job,
but I think for like joining this hackathon for me,
I would be more like understanding the AI
or agent AI from the market.
So not just what I'm doing from the company,
but also like, because I'm also in touch
with different framework, I think it's also good
that to work on the topic that are like
from the research parts or from the outside.
I guess I'll go next.
Deepi, if you want, you can go after me.
So, oh, would you?
Oh, you want me to go now?
If you want, where I can go to.
Okay, yes, that is fine.
You can go first and I can.
Okay, yeah, so I'm Josh.
Obviously I came up with like this repository
and this crazy idea, but I'll be honest guys,
like I've only gotten into
like a genetic AI machine learning
data science, computer science this year.
So I'm kind of like, sorry,
I feel like I'm stuttering a lot.
Admittedly, I'm actually very nervous
because although like I have this very ambitious idea,
I'm actually the least knowledgeable person here.
I don't have a degree, I'm still in community college.
I'm getting a degree in cinema.
I'm not getting a degree in data science
and machine learning.
I only got into AI because I was trying to write a book
and use AI to organize my book,
but because the plot was so extensive and complicated,
the context windows of the AI were too short.
So I started learning about how AI worked
and I started figuring out like, okay,
well, what is a context window?
How do prompting work?
Like basically like what happens when you take a text
and you put it into a vector embedding?
And how do you do that with like document manipulation
and stuff like that?
So I started getting into like GitHub
and like agent AI coding and all that.
And I started coming up with this idea
for just a note taking app that would take your notes,
assign JSON strings and stuff to each note
and try to contextualize the note
and embed it in a vector graph database
and kind of do like a hybrid sort of thing
where you can do just vector embeddings and translations
within your own personal notes
and then export those into JSON strings.
And then kind of like a combination between like Neo4j,
Obsidian, maybe a little bit of Figma.
And then there's one more I'm kind of missing out on.
Oh, Notion too, right?
Because we all know those.
Anyway, I tried to start creating the app.
I called it LogoMesh, it failed
because I was using AI to code the app
and I had accumulated so much contextual debt,
which is like, you know,
a combination of like technical debt
and the why behind the code, not just the what,
that it was just completely demented code.
It was just completely embarrassing.
If you go back into the repository
that I've given you access to, you'll find that.
You will find that app, you
will find all of those branches.
And it kind of just led me to take a break
from just trying to build an app
and I just began to try and understand like what AI was
and try to define a term for what I kept discovering
in my own personal projects as a consumer.
And that's what led me to kind of just unofficially
coined the term contextual debt.
And it's not until like the past two months
that I had done research, I had decided,
okay, well, what if we evaluate it?
What if we try to avoid it in some way?
And I discovered this agentic AI competition
because I had started a data science club
at my community college.
So my faculty advisor brought that to me.
And I was like, well, you know what?
This competition would be like the perfect way
for me to try and complete this project in the first place
because if I reshaped it to fit the guidelines
of the competition, then it gives me structure
that I can work with.
It gives me deadlines that I can work with.
And maybe I can try and create something tangible
and find people that are interested in the same thing.
And I may not be able to understand everything
that's going on, but I've gotten a lot better
at managing GitHub repositories and planning
and documentation and making sure that the code actually
aligns with the research.
So in that kind of way, I've kind of found my strength,
but I have to be honest with you guys.
A lot of times you guys are going to speak a lot
of languages that I'm not going to understand.
You're gonna throw a lot of terms around
that I'm not gonna understand.
And I'm gonna have to come back later to like,
transcriptive recordings of it and kind of have things
explained to me.
That doesn't mean that I'm not capable
in like managing this project.
I'm going to do my best.
But I just wanted to put that out.
I wanted to be honest with you guys.
I'm not gonna lie and say like, oh, I have a PhD
in this and that.
You would be surprised that you're quite knowledgeable
because you really, really, even if it's a short time,
you've, you've dicked a little bit.
And I think some of the things you're saying might apply
to some of us here in one way or the other.
AI is a very broad field.
There are a lot of things that you even mentioned
in this repository that I've never heard of.
Yeah, it's really broad field.
It's an amazing learning experience.
Yeah, it's new enough that like lots of things
that are coming up is new enough that like,
as long as you can learn
quickly, I think you can definitely
be ahead of the goal.
Yeah.
Yeah, and I think also don't be just too humble Josh.
I think also not just about the experience because I feel
like especially with AI topic right now,
everything come really quick.
Like almost every month there's a new topic.
Even you start researching this year.
I think if you don't keep it up, like,
I feel like already lacking a little bit,
like not reading the latest research paper or the topics,
then I already don't know what's happening right now.
So maybe your, your information or your knowledge
is already up to date and then me.
Yeah, so.
LLMs just came to light two years ago and now,
like wait has gone.
Yeah, so I still remember when like chat GPT two came out
or it's been so crazy, especially with the video generation
stuff like that, that stuff is freaky.
That's what got me into it.
Cause you know, Google Bayo three came out when I started
some college classes, I was looking at it.
I was like, I can barely discern this between reality.
And you know, I got better at
it eventually, but it's getting
so good that it's scary.
And you know, that uncally
that uncanny Valley that we're in
right now, it's closing up, it's closing up.
So we're going to see some
pretty impossible things come out
probably within the next 10 years.
I want to be prepared for that.
I want to be one of the people
that understands that instead
of just a consumer.
Cause yeah, I'm, you know, one of my biggest fears is being
controlled by that kind of stuff.
But, you know, getting into this field has been like really
enlightening for me.
It's kind of erased a lot of fears that I have AI.
It's definitely opened up new ones as well, but I feel like
understanding it has been just really, really rewarding.
I feel like, yeah.
Anyway, Deep D would, yeah.
Would you like to kind of give an intro?
Oh sure.
Thank you.
Hi everyone.
I am Deep D.
I'm from Georgia, USA.
And I have experienced in multiple areas in software
development recently and technical program management,
program management, engineering management.
Right now I'm working as a data scientist and I love data,
but I've also done a lot of AI ML programs,
but not gen AI.
So this is a great competition, the gen AI,
and glad to find Josh on the team.
You know, he has done some great work,
which I read through about contextual debt and looking
forward to working with all of you on this,
in this competition and in this team.
So I have done a lot of AI ML, like supervised learning,
unsupervised learning, NLP, and also neural networks,
but mostly on the applied sciences side,
not on the research, but gen
AI is totally different, right?
They've just gone miles ahead in,
everything.
So, but it's not tough once you understand the basics.
Yeah, this is, yeah, but this document, the contextual debt
and how we take it forward by implementing the metrics
and making the best and then taking it out,
you know, in the competition,
that would be a big, big thing for us to do.
So thank you everyone.
Thank you, Josh.
And I sent LinkedIn request to every one of you.
I think I already sent you a request.
Yes, yes, you are already connected.
Yes, I got your request a few days ago, I think.
Josh sends yours.
Yes.
Yeah.
Oh, okay, okay.
Thank you.
Oh, and Gira, I think we actually have another person
in Germany too.
I put his LinkedIn in the chat a few minutes ago.
Oh, another one?
Oh.
Allah, so I'm gonna meet with him potentially late tonight
if I'm not too tired when he wakes up.
Cause it says he's in Germany.
So I was hoping maybe you could connect with him
and kind of pick his brain.
He seemed pretty interested in the project.
He had some kind of,
oh, he actually had some questions for us.
So if you guys want like later in the meeting,
we can kind of cover those.
Okay, I'll just give a quick intro as well.
Just overall.
So I'm Samuel.
I'm actually a year for
biomedical engineering student in NUS.
But I've been working in like, on like,
AI, ML stuff, self-taught for about like five years.
Done two internships at like two of the research labs
in Singapore.
One on like a kind of like signal propagation using AI, ML,
some computer vision stuff.
And similarly, I also did computer vision with
some A star, so science research lab.
Yeah.
And after that, I spent one year in Silicon Valley.
Basically first I was with data science.
I was doing data science with a battery company.
They're called Q-Burg.
They were trying to put batteries on planes, basically.
The problem now is that batteries are too heavy.
So they were trying to make this like really energy dense
battery that could like basically be on planes
and power planes.
But I was on the data science team for that.
And, but they closed down.
So I had to find another job.
Which was actually a good thing.
Because the next company I worked at basically was
this company working on Gen. AI for manufacturing firms.
So basically they were trying to automate a lot of like
the sales processes for these legacy manufacturing firms.
Because the current process is really manual.
They do like basically customer sending purchase orders
like in all sorts of formats.
And the salesperson will have to look through each format.
And there's a central database,
but the customers don't follow that.
So they just try their best to match
based on the customer's request.
And it takes up a lot of the sales people's time.
So we were basically using like OCR,
optical character condition,
and like a few of like the cutting edge models
to like kind of pass the information
and fit that into like a table basically.
So that, and do some semantics such as to basically
get up like the best information.
So I was with them for like three months.
Very interesting.
It was like five of us in a house,
a five-person house working day and night
and shipping products.
So that, and then I've also done like,
I think a lot of hackathons,
maybe one like 10 plus different hackathons.
But yeah, so okay, that's just a bit about me.
I think it's cool that Josh has self-thought
more so kind of self-thought still learning as well.
And I think it's always great to meet people
who are interested to learn and do new things,
which I think is all of you guys.
So exciting stuff.
Sweet.
That's awesome.
Yeah, it's really cool to know
that somebody else here is self-taught as well.
I definitely have a lot of imposter syndrome.
I'm getting over that, but I don't know,
just being able to kind of like build off
of each other's strengths.
It's just a great feeling.
Sorry.
Okay.
Yeah, okay.
So since we're kind of done with the icebreakers right now,
I was, let's see what kind of agenda that I had
for the rest of the meeting.
And it's, this is open.
This is totally like modular here.
We don't have to follow this through the T to the T.
But I just kind of wanted to give us a little bit
of a foundation to work with.
Okay.
So we all kind of like understand what contextual that is,
the code AI code that works,
but it lacks intent reasoning and safety
that it kind of parallels AI agents themselves.
LLMs, they kind of mimic reasoning.
They kind of simulate it,
but they're not exactly self-aware.
I kind of wanted to talk about the cyber-sensorial agent
a little bit.
Do you guys have any like takeaways
from the approach that's being used
in like the planning and documentation to describe that?
Does any aspect of it kind of seem like confusing
or do you guys feel like it's consistent
with like the rest of the code base?
(audio cuts out)
Like using the philosophy as like agent as a judge,
using AI to like evaluate other AI processes.
And like don't, you know, the whole thing
with the contextual integrity score,
I kind of wanted to talk about that too,
because the website, it gives like a very high level
overview, but more recently I
was trying to figure out like,
okay, like what kind of logic can we lay out for this?
Because that was one of Deepti's first questions
when she looked at the repository.
And I spent a bit of time chewing over it.
And I kind of came up with some solutions.
I linked to those in the strategic master log,
which is this, you know, it's that large document
that holds like all the overarching links to it.
I think the specific document that I'm talking about
is the, yeah, here it is, the strategic pivot plan,
CIS formation, because there's like,
did you see all those functions in there
and one of those documents?
Did any of you guys come across that?
If not, I can share my screen in just a second.
I'm sure you guys are like really advanced in math
and stuff like that, but it basically just lays out
the logic of like, okay, how do we measure
each aspect of the code?
So we can kind of cover that for a little bit.
It goes into vector embeddings,
like math theory a little bit.
But yeah, I don't know if you guys had any questions
about that or?
Yeah, Josh, I think I shared some like high level
notes I had with you over Discord.
And I can just, okay, so before anyone else has like stuff,
before I dive into that, yeah.
Okay, so I think in terms of like agent as a charge,
one of the ways that I have used to like some success
in the past to like evaluate scores is,
and I think you have some of this now,
which is basically you define like a set of bricks
and maybe each thing can be assigned a score
and basically use that to, use like different kinds
of rubrics, so like maybe you have five different
assessing criteria to kind of like aggregate scores
across those things.
So that's been useful rather than just telling the agent
to like straight away give a score,
like just aggregating across different benchmarks,
getting the reason over those things
and then aggregating the score based on that,
if that's clear, yeah.
So I think in terms of like getting agent as a charge,
I mean, LMM as a judge, that's quite reasonable.
Maybe it's been done in quite a few papers.
I implemented one paper that was doing that
when I was in my previous company as well.
So yeah, on the contextual scoring thing,
I think that's fine.
For vector embeddings, and anyone else that has like
kind of experience working with like vectors and stuff
and also timing here, I think the scoring itself,
like there's the approach that we actually can take
to actually get like some core similarity between intent
and like code diffs, for example, like the changes,
which you can get from Git.
That's something we can do, but I don't think
there's a specific model that is trained for that.
And from my experience, if you do like similarity search
for embeddings, for example, it doesn't do very well
if you do like top one, if that makes sense.
Like basically you try and get like the first result,
but probably the result is like top 20.
So in terms of like encoding intent,
I think it will be useful as a metric,
but probably not a BOR and all,
even though I think that would be helpful
to help us encode it in a mathematical sense.
Yeah, so that's another thing.
And for the graph side of things,
okay, I don't wanna talk too much in detail
on this part first, but just focusing on the contextual
portion, like contextual debt, I think vectors
and using LMS to judge, makes sense,
but probably the vectors will just be like a helping
mechanism rather than like the main mechanism.
That's sweet.
Yeah, I hope that's clear.
At least let me know if like, I'm not,
yeah, if anything is confusing
cause I think different, maybe I'm not communicating
as well as I could, yeah.
I think that's, yeah, that's kind of coming across to me,
but does anybody else have questions about that?
Like, are we on the same page?
It's okay if we're not, because I'm gonna be,
so I'm gonna be providing the transcript
of this meeting afterwards to everybody
so that we can kind of review,
cause I know we're covering a lot today.
I'm definitely gonna need stuff simplified to me.
So I'm just kind of rolling with the punches here.
But that sounded good to me.
So I kind of wanted to cover this document.
I don't know if you guys, do you guys all have access
to the GitHub repository right now?
Okay, everybody, okay.
So this one specifically goes into,
did what you were talking about kind of reference
any of this stuff, Samuel?
Because this stuff like throws out a bunch of stuff
on like basically like, oh man, how do I simplify this?
I guess semantic density.
Is that a familiar term for you guys, semantic density?
I have a guess, but I have one, we'll see.
Okay, this is definitely gonna be a--
Let me check if my guess is correct.
I also wanted to say it sounds familiar,
but I think it's a good question. Yeah, I think it's a good question. Yeah, I think it's a good question. It sounds familiar, but you wouldn't be sure.
What I'm guessing it means too is that it's like
how much detail is in the structure of words, right?
Because like, I'm guessing an example of like loose,
like something that isn't semantically dense would be like,
you know, the boy crossed the street.
Something that would be semantically dense would be
like the male age six to eight years old, Brown hair.
He stepped with his right foot
and then step with his left foot
from the North side of the asphalt,
all the way, you know, stuff like that, right?
That's what I'm guessing semantic density is
like a very compressed nutshell of how it's used
in like LLM systems.
But anyway, this document,
it goes into some really complicated to me functions.
Okay.
It talks about like vector embeddings and stuff like that.
And I was just hoping like maybe you guys would be able to
like not exactly tell me what it means,
but whether or not it has any relevance
to the ideas that you have.
And ironically, it's a
semantically dense document in itself.
I barely understand it, but from what I understand,
it's basically trying to come up with the logic
for each parts of the contextual integrity score.
Like going back to the website,
it kind of bases it on those three pillars.
I'm sure everybody's familiar with that too, right?
It's architectural integrity.
I think it's test integrity.
And then there's one more.
Let me see if we can.
Rationale?
Yes, it's rational integrity score, which is the Y.
And that kind of exists in the documentation
or at least even just code comments
in the functional requirement of the code itself.
So what this document, which contains like
a bunch of chicken scratch to me personally,
it kind of tries to find the rationale
for evaluating that stuff.
And honestly, I was hoping we could chew on it
over the next week and figure out
if it's something that we wanna pursue deeper
because it has a pretty big variance
from some of the plans that I have laid out
for this project, which don't exactly go into any detail
of how exactly we do evaluate using those three pillars.
Like, there's high level overviews
of how we use the structure of that
to come up with a weighted score at the end.
But this document, like it goes
into a proposed specific structure.
So yeah, I kind of just wanted to talk about that.
I'm sorry if it kind of got us off track a little bit,
but yeah, because this is pretty much one
of the most recent bits of research I've done.
And it's the first time that I've actually kind of
hit a brick wall in my understanding
because I'm not very good at math.
I'm not very good at like logic and functions like that.
It's not my forte.
So I was hoping that maybe you guys,
your PhD students, maybe you guys
had some familiarity with this.
It's okay if you don't, we can work with that.
This document started from some way.
Is it like, this is just focusing on the architecture?
Yeah, yeah, kind of just, sorry.
Yeah, this would kind of be the logic
that the architecture would be built to follow
for the contextual integrity score.
But honestly, it's really dense for me.
So I was just kind of hoping to see what you guys had
as an opinion on it, but it's okay if it's kind of,
like it's okay if it's like too distracting to cover today
because I haven't really had enough time
to compare it to the rest of the code base yet.
Like it's a lot, it's a lot.
You guys saw the link that I put in the chat, right?
Like are you guys looking at it right now?
Yeah, one of the things I looked at
was the copyright edition paper.
Oh yeah.
I haven't copyrighted anything yet.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's just a suggestion.
So I'm on my phone now,
so it's a little difficult to like look at the code.
When you're referring to like semantic density,
there's a paper about it.
Is that like the thing you're talking about?
Like there's a paper that actually writes about
semantic density.
So I was--
Please, if you could share it though, that would be good.
Oh sure, yeah.
I definitely need an introduction to a lot of these terms
that are thrown around here.
Sure.
I would say what is contained in the paper might be,
like it could be useful, but I think in a,
okay like I need to look a little deeper at it
because I just skimmed it.
It's crazy.
Basically like the point is that it needs sampling.
So basically like what that means is you need to like
generate multiple responses from the LLM
in order to kind of get,
okay let me send over the paper before I start rambling.
Is it really with uncertainty quantification?
Yes, that's the one I think.
Should be the first one when you search semantic density.
Yeah, so in a real world use case,
I don't think we would do a lot of,
we could do multiple samples,
but I don't think we would,
but okay, we can look a bit more,
I'll look a bit more into it and see
and dive into some of like the equations,
but I would say for determining this,
some form of semantic similarity might be enough.
Nothing crazy, but I could be wrong
and I think definitely we should look more into like
some of these details that,
yeah, just off the top of my head,
we might not need to like overly complexify it,
but yeah, I think it'd be good
if people could look into the paper
and let me know if you have different thoughts.
And this just from my skimming anyway.
Yeah, so it depends on how we want to scope it
that might not be super necessary.
But it's an interesting concept in terms of how you get.
Okay, sweet.
Basically to figure out how uncertain, yeah.
Uncertain, certain responses of the LNN,
it's more of like confidence in the response.
Gotcha, okay.
Okay, that makes more sense.
Okay, sweet.
So yeah, I really didn't wanna get too much off track
because like we, you know, so far,
there's a pretty good solid plan in here.
And we have about, what's the deadline, December 19th?
We have a set amount of time
that we have to complete a purple agent.
So I do wanna be realistic with time management.
I don't wanna get too crazy in these deep rabbit holes
and like alter the plan to a certain point
where it becomes impossible for us to complete it
by the deadline.
That is a concern that I have.
So yeah, so I'm, but yeah, that's good.
I'm glad that we could kind of cover that today.
In terms of, I'm trying to find the onboarding agenda.
Here we go.
Okay, yeah, so has everybody cloned the repository
to like their personal computer and tried to, you know,
just poke around at the code a little bit,
you know, installed all the modules and stuff.
Did the Docker, did the Docker window work and all of that?
I'll be really straight.
I have not tried to run a Docker,
I've just been looking through the code
and some other documents.
Okay, okay.
So the Docker should be working.
I made sure it was all cleaned up, you know,
everything's up to spec.
So, yeah, so it's kind of,
because there's kind of a point of criticality.
There's like in terms of the project plan,
and then there's like that recovery plan
that I created on November 13th,
which was created after I compared the current plan
before that to a big paper that was done on like
what the judges are going to expect,
how our competition is going to be scored.
Stuff like the, I think it's Auth0,
that company that's sponsoring,
they're going to want to see some kind of compatibility
with our project and the integration with that.
The agent-agent kind of platform too,
for how agents are going to communicate with each other,
that kind of standard.
And then of course the agent meets
software developer kit too.
So I've kind of been working off that plan,
I've been building off of that plan,
the one that was formulated on November 13th,
it's called the recovery plan.
So I've been building off of that
and making sure that the code is good, it doesn't bug.
Been testing it, making sure
that the Docker loads properly.
But we really do need to formulate a blueprint
for the contextual integrity score,
because it has to be a rigorous formula.
It has to contain logic,
and it can't just be like a rubric how it's outlined now.
So I wanted to kind of give an update and be like,
well, I have to adapt the plan yet again
to accommodate those proposed formulas.
And then we can always tweak those formulas later on,
but there has to be logic there initially
for us to be able to work with.
So that's kind of why I was hoping
that we could prioritize finalizing
the research paper revisions.
I'm not gonna do any copywriting or stuff anymore.
It was suggested to me that I copyrighted
like this initial paper that I created,
but it's honestly just all AI generated.
The idea is valuable,
but I don't think we have to copyright anything right now.
Also, I've never written a
research paper or anything before,
so I could honestly really use your guys' advice
from an academic standpoint,
because I don't know the formal process for this.
But yeah, we do need to revise the paper
and kind of come to an understanding
of whether it's consistent and it's logic.
So I'm going to create a Discord server
and kind of put some key documents in there
when it comes to revising the research paper
and kind of explain what documentation we already have.
Of course, everything that it's referenced in that paper,
it's available in those documents.
So you can kind of rabbit hole.
You can see where claims are referencing
other research papers and all that.
And then when it comes to the workshop,
everything, so the foundation is set, okay?
The foundation is set in this repository.
Everything is just waiting for
those mathematical blueprints.
So that's gonna be the tricky stuff, especially for me.
But I think we can do it.
I think we can come to an understanding with it.
All of that document that I shared in the Google Meet chat,
that was generated by Google Gemini to propose an example.
So I think what we can do is we can take that logic
and use it as kind of a baseline,
come to understand what it's talking about
and what it means, and see if it would be a safe thing
to apply into what we're building
once we have a good understanding of what it's doing.
When it comes to the multi-agent system,
there's kind of like an orchestrator
delegating to worker structure there
that exists in the code base.
I think we need to just verify that the logic's good there,
but I think that's much simpler stuff.
And of course, there's also prototypes for the logic too,
I think.
So yeah, I just wanted to make sure
that we were kind of on the same page
when it comes to pivoting of the plan,
because I'm sure you guys have noticed the plan is kind of,
it's consistent in the documents that it's consistent,
but right now it needs to be consolidated.
And the first step to that would be consolidating
the research paper and updating it to make sure
that it goes into specifics
and proposed mathematical formulas.
And then we can adapt the plan
to mirror the research paper.
That's pretty much as simple as I can get things.
And then after that, we really just have to carry out
the plan and make sure that the code passes the test
to make sure that there's proper test structured
to evaluate the code,
and then everything should flow from there.
So right now we're basically just forming
the final foundation of the logic of the project,
which is those math formulas that I was talking about.
And then we should be good to go to start building.
Does that kind of make sense?
Do we have a good consensus on that?
To be honest, I feel like I'm kind of a little bit
behind the page or the plan,
because I think you guys already worked together
for a while, right?
And I don't know, because I just checked the GitHub
actually today a little bit,
so not really deep dive in all the section
and all the papers.
Is there any already kind of a detailed plan
or who is doing what or like toward the project?
Honestly, no.
This is the first time we've come together
to meet as a group.
I kind of just built out this foundation of the project
in my spare time.
So when it comes to the role,
I think here's what we should do.
I think we should start with what we know.
So anytime you recognize--
Sorry, have you looked at the project plan?
There is a skeletal organization that he made there.
I think that's good, starts you off.
Here, Garrett, let me send you...
So there's the document that I
think that you should look at
is called the strategic master log.
And I'm gonna send that to you in the Google Meet chat.
And it's basically a bird's eye view of the documentation
and its structure in the repository.
And it gives kind of like a very simple explanation
of each document.
And what I'm going to do this next week is kind of just
come up with a plan on how to consolidate all of that.
Because everything's in all of these different locations.
Everything's timestamped,
so you can tell when everything was created.
But honestly, I agree with Garrett.
It's all the documentation.
It may be consistent and it may be evolving,
but it's all over the place in the repository.
And it's confusing.
It's confusing even for me.
I'm barely able to hold it all together myself.
So like I said, I think it's
good that we're kind of getting
this confusion out here in the open,
because it's just a little hill that we're gonna get over.
I'm sorry, I'm talking too much.
I have to share the link.
Yeah, it's okay.
I also created, this is something that helped me
and just see everything like a little nicer.
I created a, it's under a branch called feed slash docs.
You guys can take a look.
Basically it just adds a docs for an onboarding folder
with like a HTML file.
I just prefer looking at that than a Markdown file.
HTML file with like all the links.
It's basically the master log,
but with like links and summaries to each thing.
So it just helped me like kind of understand
the interconnections faster.
Yeah, so you guys can take a look at that as well.
Yeah, basically just--
Sorry, where can I find that again?
Yeah, so there's a branch.
I hope I pushed it.
Oh, I actually, I merged it with the master branch today.
So we're using the master now.
Yeah, it's just an onboarding folder.
Yeah, onboard, yeah, yeah, yeah, here it is.
It's in the root folder.
Just open the index.html, then there's like summaries
and links.
It might have missed like maybe some stuff,
but like I think it's helpful just to really quickly get
onboarded, what's what's been happening.
Yeah, it's just basic should be the same thing
as like the Markdown just like, just prettier.
Yeah, so I think that helped me get onboard.
I actually only looked at a repository yesterday as well,
because I just got access,
but that helped me like kind of understand a little bit
of like the history and what's been going on.
Yeah. Oh, here,
I'll share my screen and we can also--
Which one is that, Samuel?
Is it in onboarding folder?
Yes, and then just open the index.html in your browser.
And then you can click into the front stuff.
Okay, thank you. Yeah.
Here we go.
Oh, okay, thank you. Yeah, so this is it.
This is really nice.
Yeah, and then if you scroll down,
there's like links to each different kind of summaries
of each document, and if you want, you can type in.
Oh, this is perfect. So you just--
Thank you. Yeah, yeah.
This is so good. I'm onboarding.
We should have started with this.
(laughing)
Okay, yeah, I'm hoping this is gonna clear stuff up too.
Yeah, I really appreciate you guys bearing with this,
because I know it's kind of a big undertaking.
It's a lot to take in.
But I think as soon as we figure out
how to incorporate the logic that's in the research folders
of the documentation folder,
as soon as we incorporate that into a consistent document,
and then we can be ready to incorporate that document
and adjust the plan.
So what I typically do is whenever I create a plan
for coding anything in the repository,
I come up with a high level idea, and I take that idea,
and I come up with a gap analysis.
And I usually take an AI agent,
and I prompt it to review all of the core foundational code
in the repository and compare it to the plan
that I have in mind.
And I have a come up with a gap analysis document.
So it usually tells me where things connect,
where things are already formed and created,
where things contradict each other
from the plan that I want to implement
into what I'm building compared to what exists.
So when I come up with further research
that comes up with math functions
for the contextual integrity score,
and it comes up with all of this logic,
the logic itself may be consistent,
and it may fit well into the high level view of the plan.
But when it comes to the,
if you go to section three of the navigation guide,
you'll find, I'm sorry, section two of the website.
Is everybody on the HTML page,
or can they at least see my screen?
Yeah.
Okay.
Okay, screen now.
Right, so if we go to section two,
here's the workshop, the historical technical plan, right?
We have this thing titled the recovery plan.
This is a plan that I've created from a gap analysis
between a very large research document of previous
and current agent beats guidelines rules,
kind of implied rules in terms of like sponsorships
and all that.
So I came up with this plan earlier
about almost 10 days ago on the 13th.
And I started enacting that plan
and putting it into the code base.
And I stopped at a certain point of the plan.
And then I started realizing, yeah, there's no logic
in how we're actually going to evaluate
with the contextual integrity score.
When I met with Deep D last week,
she kind of brought that up.
She was like, well, how are we going to structure
each pillar of the contextual integrity score?
Like what tools are we going to use?
What logic are we going to use?
And I was like, wow, that's a good question.
Because everything in that is still high level.
It hasn't been cut out into logic yet.
So I went and I came up with some logic using AI
and AI proposed some stuff to me.
That's that really complicated document
that I shared with you guys
like 20 minutes ago, that GitHub.
It's called the 20251118 proposed section 2.2.md.
That link, it's basically eligible for me.
So what I need to do, and that's in the,
you can find that in the cutting edge section,
strategic pivots.
That's where all the research is.
So if you want to see like research that goes deeper
into the base level ideas, you go to the docs folder,
you go to the strategy and IP folder within that,
and then you'll find some papers.
And those papers get into more detailed logic.
So that logic has not been incorporated into the plan yet.
So what I have to do this
upcoming week is I have to come up
with another gap analysis.
I have to analyze the entire state of the current state
of the repository, which is well-documented.
It's been rigorously tested and reviewed.
I have to do the same thing for the recovery plan,
which was on the 13th.
That's in section two.
That's the plan that I was carrying out.
And then I have to figure out where the gaps are
and whether there's contradictions in the plan
compared to the proposed logic that's been discovered.
And then the strategic pivot plan is highlighted
in section three.
It's basically just trying to figure out how we can
incorporate that into the current plan.
And it shouldn't be too hard.
I think we all just need to take on roles
of what we're most familiar with in terms of these plans.
Definitely pick your strengths.
My strength is organization and comparing whether documents
are relevant to each other, whether ideas align
with each other, where they contradict, where they differ.
So I'm good at that high level stuff.
If you guys find terms or anything that kind of peak out
to you that you have personal experience with,
focus on those and present your findings
in a form that best suits you.
You can either, when I create our group Discord server,
you can either just put it straight in the Discord server
and I can format it into log documents
and put those into the repository.
Or you can create your own evaluation
and you can create your own findings.
You can create your own subfolder
in the logs folder of the repository.
And you can use that just for your own needs
and organize it how you want.
So that less of your time is spent trying to understand
how to fit the form at it.
So when you guys kind of review this,
if you guys need to take personal notes
and put it in the repository,
just make your own folder wherever you wanna make it
and tell me so that I can make sure that that's clear
where to find your stuff.
I know this is like a really general kind of suggestion
that I'm making right now, but it works
because we can always kind of connect our findings together
in these weekly meetings and
through our group messages too.
So yeah, we basically need to just put things together.
Ideas are consistent in all these different sections
of the repository, but the logic that's been recently
discovered on how to organize
the contextual integrity best score,
that needs to be incorporated into the current plan
that the repository has been based off of
so that when we continue to work,
we're making sure that we have specific logic
for each way that we're taking our evaluation.
I'm hoping that that kind of provides an explanation.
You can always continue to ask me questions about it
and it's my fault that the documentation is so crazy.
So I'm going to spend this next week
kind of just helping take that on.
But yeah, if like my top recommendation is definitely
take a look at the current plan
that just has the high level stuff in it, right?
That's the one that was created on the 13th, section two,
right, that's the historical technical plan.
I've updated the code base up to task 1.2 of that plan.
So that may not be completely clear,
but you can find in the logs folder
under my co-pilot subfolder
that I've completed task 1.2 of this plan.
But where the logic deviates is currently unknown.
So I do have a gap analysis I think that currently exists,
but yeah, so I recommend like this upcoming week,
just try and understand each aspect of the repository.
The documents or the documentation
are as accurate as I can make it.
Also try and run the code too.
Try and use the readme file in the folder
to just see if you're able to install
all the modules on your computer.
You'll have to install Visual Studio Code.
It's all the instructions are outlined in the readme
for just setting up the code base itself.
So that should be too difficult.
If you guys run into issues with it, please tell me and yeah,
I'm just gonna open it up to further questions
and comments now,
because I feel like I've been talking for too long.
So.
Yeah, thanks Josh.
Thanks, Sansu.
Yeah, I really need to go through the plan
and all the stuff and try to run it by myself. So I think that's a good question. And all the stuff and try to run it by myself first
so that I can understood or understand
how exactly it works and then to give my output there.
Sure.
And I, like I said, I know this is a lot to take in.
It's okay to be confused.
It's really the way that we all work together
with our own understanding of the project
and how we specialize in our own areas of the project
and how this project is gonna develop well.
So don't worry if you don't understand everything,
just try and stick with what you know first,
find things that are recognizable for you
and make your own connections from there.
And that's probably gonna be the easiest way for you
to kind of discover how our project.
But yeah, I'm really, dude,
Samuel, thank you again for making this website
because it's just way more organized
than that Markdown file that I made.
I mean, you could just see where everything is.
The summaries help so much.
So I really appreciate that.
That was a huge help.
Did you do this in just one day?
Yeah, I did that.
(indistinct) Yeah.
So, okay.
I think I have a few questions.
Actually it's mainly admin related and that's what's new.
So I think that's a couple of things.
So it's really like,
is there a theme size limit for this hackathon?
I think that's one.
There is, it's eight people.
Okay, okay.
That's slightly interesting.
Okay, so that's the first question.
The second question is,
I saw that there is some like,
I mean, there's some requirements for the hackathon.
I think, like creating a benchmark
or evaluating some region.
So specifically like kind of what,
what are we pushing for for the hackathon specifically?
So if you don't have a,
if you ask them now,
just like,
(indistinct)
really into the hackathon,
I guess to be honest,
why is it we're pushing for now?
So that we can be very clear what we should optimize for.
Yeah, we will smash the second question.
Sorry, let me try and rephrase that.
So like you're asking what we're pushing for now,
what we're hoping to have achieved
by the deadline of the green agent phase.
Is that what you're asking?
Exactly, yeah.
Okay, sweet.
So yeah,
cause you know the website that I created,
it's very generalized, right?
So here's what I'm hoping.
I'm hoping that our project,
first of all,
like let's start with baseline, right?
We want our project to be easy to install to,
so that's why I had the Docker,
so that like all the packages are just in modules
are just easy to install, right?
Not,
what do you call it?
There's nothing gate kept about the project in the terms,
in the sense of everything that you need
to run the project is easily accessible.
I feel like I'm rephrasing what I just said.
Number three,
it has to follow the agent to agent protocol number four,
the contextual integrity score,
it has to be consistent in the sense that
when we evaluate the same code base,
I'm hoping that our end product is going to
provide a detailed scoring system
that can tell us what,
where exactly the code base that we're evaluating
or potentially,
or the purple agent, I'm sorry,
the purple agent that we're evaluating,
where exactly it falls short in certain areas,
maybe in terms of like documentation
or the logic behind the code,
so it has to be consistent, right?
So when we put something into the evaluation system,
we want to make sure that if we run it several times
on the same thing,
it's not going to spit out a bunch of different stuff.
I feel like that's kind of a simple goal,
but other than that, I feel like everything is,
would you feel like,
like for example, the,
like let's look at the recovery plan here, right?
Let's just skip it really quick, right?
So we have the core analyzer logic,
each part of the logic has to output valid complexity
and maintainability scores.
So in terms of like maintaining
what I'm assuming is the code base,
it has to output, I'm sorry,
I'm starting to lose my train of thought here a little bit.
First of all, I know I don't have to answer your question,
but does it seem like I understood your question
in the first place in terms of like,
so you're talking about our end vision, right?
For the green agent?
Yeah.
Okay.
So I think it's like,
would you say that there's kind of a gap in documentation
of like where our agent envision is?
Because, you know, I feel like there's some,
there's some like general
visions for what our green agent is.
And you can kind of decipher it based on
what the recovery plan has us enact,
but you're saying that we should probably come up
with a document that envisions the green agent
on a more detailed level, right?
Yeah, I think my name is
actually missing a little bit more.
So like there's nothing at the start of it,
I think it's like here,
I think that's quite a bit of focus
on creating a job smart.
So it's not just like creating an agent that does,
and it does balance and it adds,
but we need to,
and if any of you have a different understanding,
please keep with me.
We need to create like a benchmark
that kind of can be really,
like different kind of,
like basically so that,
like what you mentioned, like you predicted the key,
but I just had to do a little bit more about
like how we have to learn about building this,
but it's like, no, we're telling you.
So like, sorry, the content of like a benchmark here,
like it's like,
in, it's just so that like every time someone has a new,
at least like how every time there's a new LLM,
they're always saying that they are keeping the top score.
So the top scores is just in like different,
they're all different types.
So in our case, they will be like,
basically something that we can always make
not for the content,
but for like different use cases.
Yeah.
So you're talking like,
like baseline things that we can use to give to agents
in order to evaluate their output.
Is that what you're talking about?
Yes, correct.
So like an example is like,
for example, Gemini 3.0 just released
and then they're saying, oh, it's touching the benchmark.
Or it's like, of course those things can always be king,
but it does give like a baseline understanding
of how good it can be said,
a specific class, let's say a software development,
that have three bench or software development.
That's a class that is commonly like very useful
for like coding agents,
like a Google Junes or whatever it is.
And similarly for us,
we wanna be able to evaluate the contextual integrity.
So we wanna kind of create a benchmark for that.
And this is my understanding of like,
what is the impact upon part of this
to the data system we've been on,
which is like something that should be done.
And for our own use case,
as we like work on this agent,
and we evaluate like different elements,
like we can kind of see how well like different elements
work on this benchmark.
So I get them this one,
like different about map,
if that's all the panel, yeah.
That's good. Like how we get doing it.
Yeah, that's good.
Okay, well, since we're kind of coming out of this
with a bit of a cybersecurity angle,
I was thinking maybe we could come up
with a few benchmark ideas for like cybersecurity apps
or maybe I wanna say environments.
I don't have any specific ideas yet,
but I'm really glad that you brought that up.
Did you happen to have any ideas for that yet?
Or maybe we could set a time later
to kind of hone that a little bit.
Sure, yeah.
I think that is, sorry, yeah.
Oh, sorry.
And then in terms of like
how we present those baseline evaluation prompts
would be, in terms of like,
okay, it's tough because it's like,
are you talking about like prompts
that we would give the out,
the proposed purple agent, right?
We would give the purple agent prompts
that we've already pre-structured
that we would eventually use to see
if the agent has completed those tasks in a way
that doesn't accumulate contextual debt,
which relates back to those prompts.
Is that kind of--
Yeah, something like that.
Something like that. So prompts, yeah.
So prompts for the purple agent to build something,
and then we wait for the purple agent to build something,
and then we evaluate what it builds against the prompts
and the why and the what behind those prompts, right?
Yeah, I think we need to think a bit more
about how to flesh out the benchmark.
I had people like kind of
discuss this another time as well,
but like just wanted to get some clarity on
where we're at.
But I sent some of the benchmark,
I think they are looking at
as the competition in the group.
It's in the Discord somewhere,
if you are, but I sent it in the chat.
And that's just some standard like benchmarks
that people use to evaluate like this.
Sweet, that's kind of different,
different types of agents for different tasks,
but what we are doing is slightly different,
and I'm actually not super sure
how we're gonna frame the engine itself.
So I think some, from the benchmark itself,
I don't know if any of you have experienced
like building these kind of benchmarks
in a different field of trying,
but the idea is that we wanna make a task
that we can evaluate like any agent on,
if that makes sense.
It's like a test, yeah.
It's a test that you can just run
without putting in a yes,
but yeah, like just run different agents on
and then see if I can do it.
So we need like some kind of any real life,
we need some sort of rubric to figure out what always,
how we're measuring the content for that.
So yeah, the one,
yeah, just throwing some new thoughts.
So like, we think about it and like,
think if we put the discuss some,
how we really wanna put that,
because I'm still looking through the rubrics,
I think that's like one of the things
that they do that specifically for this,
which is like creating a benchmark,
extend it and our benchmark,
the ideas that they want things to be that,
basically help the community to like,
evaluate agents in the formulas.
Yeah, so maybe like next time,
they'll have to try and evaluate
how good they are on our contextual
information score, like,
and specifically for security,
I think I have some questions on that,
like how we're gonna link like this content
for that here with like security wise,
because I think that's like in different concept as well.
But yeah, so I think that's about it,
just like some thoughts,
some questions I have on that,
but like direction wise,
it would be good specifically for this type of problem
to figure out what's, what everyone is, yeah.
Okay, okay.
Anybody else wanna add on to that first time or?
I don't think I know anything so much.
Okay, okay, but I see what you're getting at,
and I agree, I think it's really important.
I would appreciate it,
so once I get a group server up and running,
which will be like whenever this meeting wraps up,
I'll invite all you guys to it,
if you could rephrase that question
or basically goal for us
and just put it as a message into the chat,
that would be really helpful.
And then I'll provide the script,
the transcript too,
and kind of format that as an agenda.
Hopefully it will get picked up on that too, so.
But yeah, that's good,
we have to figure out whether or not
the plan currently addresses any aspect of that.
I feel like it hopefully touches on a little bit of that,
but maybe not so much in the specifics.
Yeah, yeah.
And then I guess the last,
another admin is on like commitment wise,
I like, I'll be able to pick another paper here.
Yeah, how much?
Sorry, it's just, sure, sorry,
can you hear me now? Yeah.
Yeah, so I think it's like commitment wise.
And we can also discuss this like,
after we look through the,
like just how we commit and then,
and I guess if we're having between meetings,
like when's it gonna be,
and I also like stuff like that.
(laughing)
Just so we can have a view of that, yeah.
So when you say the word commit,
are you talking about like committing to the repository
or your time commitment?
Which one?
I mean, for repositories, I don't know,
it's pretty standard, we just make a branch and stuff.
I think we should all kind of be a bit familiar with that,
but talking more of like working.
Like team commitment.
How much time, yeah, exactly.
How much time can you put into this?
And what kind of what stuff
are you interested in working on?
And if the stuff you're interested in working on
is not given out,
like then like think about it.
(mumbles)
That's good.
Yeah, if we can all outline
what our interests are in this repository,
in the group chat, they'll create later,
that will kind of help with the baseline commitment.
I think, I would say don't overexert yourself.
I think part of the commitment is going to be in,
sorry, I'm losing my train of thought again.
But yeah, I agree with everything that you said.
I think that we should definitely come up with
some kind of like team consensus document
of what aspects of the project
that we're personally committing ourselves to,
to ensure that there are no gaps in the repository
and that nothing is being kind of just looked past.
Hopefully that kind of just rephrased what you said, right?
Is that what you said?
Yeah, Facebook.
Yeah, I agree.
And I feel like maybe like first,
I think we all go through the repository by ourself.
And I think that because I mean,
when I checked the submission requirement,
I mean, or the judging criteria,
I think that the core is about
how do we define the benchmark
and benchmarking and all the stuff.
But other than that, there's still many minor stuff.
Like for example, you need to prepare
a clean repository, clear instruction,
or even a three minute video.
And I think all those minor things we also need to plan.
So I think maybe after everyone go through the repository
and if we meet next time,
or we just commute in the discord or in the chat,
then we can also write down maybe who to do what.
Because I feel like maybe we can have one person,
maybe Josh or Sam you, you can deep dive more
in the benchmarking part.
But I think for me, at least for the moment,
I feel like I would like to have
a like grounding understanding of it.
But then maybe I can also focus on more the coding quality
or how can we make it better?
So I think we can also make like kind of
like specific for everyone
so that we can all contribute to the project as a team
then when we submit it.
So.
Okay, perfect.
Yeah.
Sorry, go ahead Finzi.
Yeah, I just wanted to add to that.
That's really, really necessary
because I think we have like four weeks or something
for the whole thing to be done.
I thought I had a theoretical understanding
when I went through the repo,
but I need to run it on my, yeah.
Now I see that there was a lot that I didn't really look at
just like Garret says.
So it's important if we know
if we are going to be meeting every week and when,
maybe even from now.
But if we are not even able to talk about it now,
we should do that like as soon as
because of time constraint.
Yeah.
Sure.
Yeah, that's really good.
And I was hoping,
so when we do kind of pick out our roles
and make sure that like what you said,
even just making the presentation video
and the clean repository and the instructions,
there's kind of, there's a little bit of a table,
a role table for that in the project plan,
markdown document for that.
But I feel like we could totally tweak those roles
to make sure that,
you can just take inspiration from that table.
And yeah, when it comes to just like discovery
of the repository, yeah, please, please clone it.
And just to make sure that everything runs
without any module install errors and stuff.
From then on, you can do some little testing with that.
But I guess main priority is like,
I know what runs on my machine.
I have a Windows 10 desktop,
you know, 64 bit or whatever.
But yeah, try and just make sure it runs on your stuff too.
If you guys run into any issues,
just please, please document them.
Yeah, I really agree.
That's really good that you're following the rules.
Are you guys good?
So I know that you guys are in
kind of in different time zones.
Like Garrett, you're here at 3 a.m.
So depending on what you're gonna be doing later today,
I don't know if you're gonna go back to sleep,
take a nap or it's like, it's okay.
So it's 7.30 my time.
What time is it for you?
Now it's 4.30.
Dude, thank you.
I think we should let the man get to sleep.
Yeah, dude.
So I was thinking like, okay, every Friday we can do,
I think it would be good for us to potentially pair up
depending on time zones.
So if you guys are like,
if it's really late in the night for some of you guys,
maybe a little bit earlier on this Friday.
For you, Garrett, I was hoping potentially
maybe you could meet with me in a few hours.
This would be one in the morning my time.
So 7.30, 8.30, 9.30, 10.30, 11, 12.
And then so in five and a half hours,
would you be free in five and a half hours
because I have a teammate
who's in Germany as well, I think.
It would be around.
Okay, so.
I think that would be around 10 in the morning for you.
So how many hours after?
So five and a half hours from now,
I'm going to be meeting with somebody else
who I think lives in Germany too.
Okay, I think that would be about 10 or 11, right?
So yeah, I need to check if I could still wake up,
to be honest.
It's okay, no worries, no worries.
But I'm saying like next week.
Ah yeah, I mean.
Next week, do that instead.
And then, because that would help for eight,
I'm a night owl, right?
I like to stay up until 10 or 11 AM your time.
So I can always just meet with you then.
And then just record other,
I think if we meet asynchronously,
I think everybody should record their meetings.
And then I can help with transcript organization
and all that.
We can all be on the same page that way.
We don't have to meet everybody at once.
But yeah, are Fridays slash Saturday mornings
a good day for you guys to do?
For me, this time works,
but even later in the night works.
But during the day, during the weekdays,
I don't have time.
But I'm also a night person like you are.
Yeah, so most of the nights I'm able to do extra,
other works other than my PhD work here.
So.
Okay, sweet.
Yeah, and don't burn yourselves out.
You can commit to as much as you feel comfortable doing.
The gaps will get filled some ways.
It's gonna be, it'll work out.
Yeah, I agree with scheduling.
So we can try and figure out
how people can kind of pair up.
And then we can just do asynchronous meetings
and then just consolidate the updates
into some kind of channel,
some kind of log folder just for team updates.
Yeah, that makes sense, right?
Yeah, I think asynchronous meeting
and also add like, I think more importantly,
we have kind of team channel.
I think GitHub is actually also good
that we can make use of it.
But like, for example,
I think there's some Microsoft planners
we can also use to plan up the task
and with the deadline or kind of stuff.
Yeah, then we can kind of also send with chat and yeah.
So not really need to do it like every time
it face to like on a call,
but maybe once a week,
but then we will like frequently talk in a team chat.
So yeah, that would be great.
Okay, perfect.
Okay, let's see.
Wow, we've met for an hour and a half now.
So I'm gonna invite all of you guys
to this server that I just created.
Well, I created the server for months ago
but there's nobody in it.
And I'm just making sure,
see if I can find everybody here.
Okay, let's see.
I'm having trouble seeing all of the usernames here.
Encarceron, is that you Samuel?
Yeah, that's me.
Okay, sweet.
I just sent you an invite.
Yeah.
Oh, come on.
Sorry Hadiza, do you know your Discord username?
Yeah, I think you should be hadix.
I found it.
Hadiza.
There we go.
Same thing, yeah.
Okay, so I think I just sent everybody an invite.
If you haven't received an invite, please let me know now.
Deep T, I think I sent you a name.
All right.
So, and then I'll give you all of you guys
moderator access.
So if you want to create channels, change channel names
or do whatever you want with the server, that's fine.
That'll be a good balancing point
for how we can better organize the GitHub repository
to accommodate our needs and preferences.
Like I said, logs are a mess.
So we'll work with what we got now,
but what's come to a consensus on how we will
organize our logs and documentation in the repository
through the server.
And then we can figure it out from there.
Is it, am I missing anything?
Does that make sense?
Yeah, it does.
I know the task right now is still in chunks.
I don't know if before or by the next time we meet,
we're able to break them down.
Maybe we all have gone through the repository
and have understood everything in there.
Yeah, because what we call in the end
is very high level.
Yes, if we could break it together into smaller chunks,
that would be less.
I don't know how to put it.
It would be less the way it works on the brain.
I don't know the English word, but.
It's okay.
So when it is small, small, small, small like this,
it's yeah.
It's-
We were able to achieve that before
or by the next time we meet.
Yeah, for sure.
And I was thinking maybe we could make
like one channel for each thing.
It's okay if we have a ton of channels.
We can do channel.
I don't know if you guys use Discord a lot,
but there's this thing where
you can group channels together.
So, we could have a,
just a document organization section
and then a channel for each, whatever.
Or a, and then we can have a planning section
and then a channel just for planning
the contextual integrity score
and the math logic behind that
and how we're comparing that to the code base
and just a couple of examples there.
But yeah, we have a really good starting off point.
And yeah, I think it'll take us kind of a week
to come to a general consensus on how to move forward.
So I'm not expecting any code to be updated
unless you guys find bugs in the code.
So right now it's kind of just discovery,
making sure we're all on the same page with the code
and figuring out how to organize the documents
and the current logs to better sync our understanding.
And then we can move forward with refactoring the plan
and getting all that benchmark logic out there.
So, oh, before, I feel like this is a good time
for us to start to wrap up.
Before I let you guys go, I wanna see if,
because I know that somebody had some questions
that they wanted to ask us.
Here we go.
It was, yeah, it was Allah.
So he also lives in Germany.
Maybe next week you can meet him, Garrett,
but he'll see the recording from this meeting.
Yeah, so he had some questions over.
He had some pretty specific questions.
If we've discussed the choice of LLMs for the evaluator
and the evaluated agents, you know what?
I'm just going to, I'll invite him to the Discord server
and then I'll paste his questions in the chat.
Because I feel like if I read them now,
we would just kind of go into discussion
and I don't wanna do that right now, tired.
But yeah, guys, thanks for coming to this meeting.
This was a lot.
So I will save this recording
and I'll have a transcript summary of the meeting
in about an hour from now.
And I'll just put it in the Discord.
I'll put, I'll invite Allah to the Discord too.
And I think we should be good to go for that.
There were a couple people that were interested in coming
and they didn't make it.
I don't know if it's because they didn't understand
that it was gonna be in this time zone or not.
Cause I heard from them earlier today,
but I think there were two people
that couldn't make this meeting.
So I'll try and get them up to date too
and assume that they're still interested.
Other than that, I think we have a good solid team of five.
So this has been really exciting.
And hey, I just wanted to say thank you
for bearing with me on this, okay?
Because like, I'm really ambitious,
but it takes, I'm sure you guys have noticed,
like you guys asked me something
and it takes me a couple of times
to really understand what you're saying.
That's why I'm recording everything.
So yeah, I just wanna say, like, thank you.
Thank you for participating in this.
And yeah, that's it.
Thank you for putting it together.
I think it's going to be a running process for me.
Yeah.
So thank you.
Yeah, if you guys have like, like, I don't know,
like I guess I'll do it.
I haven't had much experience with like events and stuff.
Like if you have questions, like I'm up with stuff,
like I can probably like answer more questions, I think.
So that's like, feel free to ping me when you can.
Yeah, okay.
I don't know everything.
I'm still learning.
So if I don't know, I can also learn a few things.
So feel free to like this in the channel,
ping you, you know, like figure this out,
try to like learn as quickly as possible
and like really build something.
Yeah.
Thank you, Samu.
Can we call you Sam?
Feel free, feel free.
Yeah.
Okay.
Sweet.
Yeah.
Yeah, thanks, Sam.
Thanks, Samu.
Okay.
Great.
So yeah, I'll catch you guys later.
Just feel free to look out for that transcript summary
and all that.
I'll pace the questions from now on.
And yeah, I guess that's it for tonight.
Garrett, get some sleep.
Thank you so much for staying up.
It was so nice meeting all you guys.
Nice meeting you, Hadiza.
Nice meeting you also.
Yeah, thank you.
It's Samu.
Nice meeting you, Dan.
Have a good one, Dan.
See you.
Bye everyone.
Bye.