I use QCLI.
So it's Amazon's coding agent.
Pretty useful.
Yeah.
So it runs on the command line, and you can sort of guide
it through which tools to use from the command line,
which sort of workspaces to look into.
It's similar to what CoPilot
does, but a lot better, I think.
And you have more control once
you're using it from the command line.
You get to sort of...
Not to open an application with a GUI, but to sort of use a
tool that you already have installed.
So say, for example, when I want to come up with...
When I want to create a JSON file, I don't like to build
the prompts by myself, so I sort of use it and tell it to
use this software that I have, this JQ...
JSON query software, and it can sort of navigate how to use
it if you give it documentation or
if it's already been trained on it.
If it's a well-known software, then
it already does know how to use it.
And you can sort of guide it through which tools that you
wanted to use, and it sort of...
Yeah, you approve each one of the commands that it comes up
with, and it does a loop where, you know, if it makes a
mistake, it sort of reiterates, and
until, yeah, it does what you ask it to.
And you can also trust it, but trust it to run commands
without your approval, but on the side, I don't trust it.
Yeah.
[Silence]
You just... Yeah, it runs... It doesn't run locally, but
you just install the QCLI thingy, and then it sort of asks
for your Amazon credentials and whatnot, and you get a free
trial, but then you might... Yeah.
At some point, it tells you, "Okay, you're
going to have to pay for the pro-lytheon."
So, I think it uses Clod in the backend. Like, most of the
work is done through, yeah, Clod.
But Amazon sort of builds the
tooling around it, and, you know...
It is. Honestly, it is.
[Silence]
I think... Yeah, yeah, I mean, that's sort
of what OpenAI Atlas does, I think, right?
And I think, for Flexity, they sort of launch the browser
that does the same thing, whereas, like, an agentic
browser, and... Yeah, I wouldn't
trust those things to be honest.
Yeah.
[Silence]
Yeah, yeah, exactly.
Yeah.
[Silence]
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
So, let me just cut into that way you refer to with
contextual depth, where it's sort of the model's doing what
you're telling it to, and then at some point, it starts to
get floppy, and then you have to intervene, and then you're
sort of reminding it what it's supposed to
do, that sort of you paying the depth, or...
So, yeah, okay, okay.
Mm-hmm.
Okay, okay.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah. Yeah.
[Silence]
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, yeah, okay, okay. Yeah, I read that
as well, yeah. Very interesting concept.
And, okay, and what you're imagining for the evaluation,
would it be like a step-by-step evaluation, or sort of a
post hoc evaluation after everything's done, or...
[Silence]
Mm-hmm.
Sorry, maybe I didn't understand those concepts well. So,
the green agent is the one that's being evaluated, and the
purple one's the evaluator, or is it something? Is it...
Yeah, okay. Mm-hmm. Which is, the
evaluator is the green agent, sorry.
Okay.
Yeah, yeah, okay. The purple's the evaluated. I think, is
there a word, a better word for
this, than the evaluated agent?
I'm looking... Yeah, okay.
But it's fine.
And...
The competing agent, okay. Since there is more than one,
and you sort of... Yeah, okay,
they're competing. Yeah, okay. Makes sense.
[Silence]
Uh-huh, okay. And...
So, the purple agents are not in our control, basically, is
what I'm trying to ask, because I know for
sure some agents do provide their reasoning.
And those are most of the open source ones, but ones like
Chat GPT, they're sort of
obscured, and cloud as well, I think.
So, if that's the thing that we're trying to evaluate, I
think we'd need to come up with a method.
Sorry, yeah. Mm-hmm.
[Silence]
Mm-hmm.
Uh, I might have just skimmed
through it, to be honest, so... Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Good.
Aha, okay. Mm-hmm.
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
[Silence]
Mm.
Okay, so...
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
So, the why is inferred, it's not provided by the agent,
the competitive agent, is it? Yeah.
[Silence]
Mm-hmm.
Uh-huh.
Okay. So, it's not inferred from the code, from the
generated code, but rather from what the agent is saying
while it's building the code.
Like, yeah, the rationale.
[Silence]
Yeah. I think the problem would be that the evaluation
would be biased towards the evaluator agent,
because it's the one inferring the rationale from the code.
But if there is another way where the competitive agent is
the one that's saying, "Okay, I
built this, but it's purpose,"
then the evaluator agent can sort of judge that and say,
"Okay, but that's not the reason
why you're supposed to do that,"
and that sort of can be quantified, I'm not sure.
Yeah, I agree. I think it would be best to request that the
competitive agent provides comments in its code or
documentation to support its code
so that we can use the code with the rationale.
[Editor's Note: This is when Josh realized that his microphone was muted in his recording software and unmuted it, beginning to explain the creative process behind the CIS score.]
When I kind of design this, I typically start out with a
high-level overview like this,
and then I try and flush it out
and try and see if there's any research papers out there
that kind of have anything to do with this.
I also use Gemini to try and generate some logic that we
may be able to work with and
then research that logic itself.
So I have a paper that kind of, I have a document I can
share with you in the
repository that goes deeper into this,
but when I shared it with the rest of the team earlier
today, I kind of realized that it was such a dense document
that we were unable to review it properly because none of
us really understood graph theory.
I'm definitely not a math major. It's a lot of logic.
I was hoping maybe you might be able to take a look at it
and see if you could decipher it, but otherwise I'm just
going to process it in the way that I
normally do and I don't understand things.
Yeah, sure. I'm happy to have a look.
Sure, let me find it. Here it is, proposed section 2.2. So
I'll just send you the link here.
Yeah, and really do not be worried if you can't understand
it. I'm still trying to piece it
together myself because it's a lot of math.
Yeah, it's math heavy.
It's very math heavy, but we do need quantifiable math and
functions for this three pillars. So
it's important that we go over this.
Cool.
I think I also had a couple of
questions. No, I think we covered.
How about the ones that you sent over Discord?
Yeah, but also, do we have, I mean, we might have to look
for a benchmark. Are we planning to
sort of come up with our own benchmark?
I think Aaron came up with that similar question too.
And sort of what would be the ground truth as well for the
scoring? So would those be like
manual annotations provided by us?
Because we can't like 100% rely on
the outputs of the evaluator, right?
I think we do ideally need some swimming in the loop.
Yeah.
Let me see.
But sorry, you were saying, yeah.
Let me see if I can find any
documentation on that really quick.
Hold on. I think I had something that mentioned that
somewhere. So I'm just running a search right now.
Sorry for the delay. There's just
so much going on with this, you know.
Not at all. I know it's like 1.30 over there.
Yeah.
Yeah, the meeting went well, but it also revealed like a
lot of confusion surrounding the
documentation because there's a lot of doc files.
And I'm in the process of consolidating those tonight.
Okay, so.
Yes, so there is a key section in this file. This is my
draft kind of research paper. This is an this is in.
Really draft. Let me see.
Okay, so this is the by the way, I
generated this. I didn't write this.
But
it's
it's relevant. Okay.
Okay, so I'll tell you where exactly you can find that
section then about to kind of cover really quick summarize.
So.
It's so if it argues for human in the loop accountability,
but it also states that those kinds of checkpoints, they're
not scalable. Like if you try and scale up.
So there's there is so in when I
was researching the competition.
It mentions asynchronous authorization is a feature that
enables human in the loop approval workflows for high
stakes actions. So it doesn't mean we
can't use it. We can definitely use it.
There is
let's see.
Okay, so
you say how you mean like well, the agents. Yeah, sorry.
I'm sorry. I didn't I didn't explain the how.
So
I don't think it's been covered deeply enough.
I need specific I'm using using my coding agent to try and
find specific practical applications of human in the
planning of the documentation.
Yeah, because a lot of some of this
has been pushed out to the point of
that logic here, but a lot of this is
kind of just like the foundation of skeleton of the code.
So I'm not sure if that's been decided yet.
Okay, give it a second.
See.
Okay.
Oh, boy. Yeah, I'm sorry. I think I think I need to.
I don't have a good answer for this question.
I know it's fine.
This is really good. And I'm glad that you brought it up.
So I think I should create a text channel called
questions really quick.
Then, yeah, if you could if you could type that question
out and then put it in the checks channel and then I can
come back to it. I'm also consolidating all of the other
questions from the team meeting to
because there was there were questions about like whether
like how we're going to handle the scoring rubric aside
from just the contextual integrity
score like a three pillars part of it.
Like, you know, what kind of
assignments we would give the purple agents.
But I guess at the same time, it's like
would that be something that the judges would do at the
same time and in order to evaluate the green agent.
It's maybe something we have to take consideration to.
I don't know. How do you how do
you feel about this? Honest thoughts?
I feel it has potential to be
honest. There's a lot of potential.
In terms of the scenario itself. I think there's like a
scenario that I kind of shared with you where it's like
sort of related to the cyber security domain where
the agents could be tasked with building something that's
I don't know, like sort of sensitive and
then the evaluator would decide whether but that would be
only for the to evaluate the quality.
So there's like three scores if I recall correctly.
There's the contextual depth,
which is evaluating the rationale.
The second one had to do with the
code itself, the architecture. Right. So
I guess that means whether it's like there's a lot of
boilerplate code and whether there's any vulnerabilities.
At least that's how I understood it. But I'm not sure.
And then there's the test. So unit test.
Honestly, I'm not too familiar with unit test.
So that's the integrity score. Yeah, I'm not too familiar
with that because I'm sort of
more of a theoretical kind of.
Yeah. Oh, it's OK. It's OK. I do know somebody.
I forgot his name. One of our teammates. He's going to be
focused more on the testing and quality of the code because
it sounds like he's kind of specializes in that.
OK. I'm hoping he can provide some feedback on that too.
But yeah, like this scenario and contextual relevance of
like the test suite against the requirements of the code.
But but yeah, the scenario is the thing
right that we're supposed to be discussing.
Oh, sorry. Yeah, no, no worries.
I was asking as well. I wasn't.
I'm not sure. Also, this was sort of a
question and a statement. So is it. Yeah.
Like in terms of how we're going
to be testing the purple agent.
Yeah. So the task that it will be told to.
OK. Yeah. So what I'm imagining right now is that we
present purple agent a certain prompt.
We have it in some point some kind of like right. We use
the agent agent protocol to submit that prompt to it.
And then it writes either. That's the
thing. Like how deep can we get in this.
Can we have it write a series of code files that kind of
work with each other like even to the to the extent of like
importing Python models and stuff.
We might be able to get that far. Who knows. Yeah. I mean,
honestly, I think you should play around a bit with QCLI
and it will sort of give you an idea of how how capable
these agentic these coding agents are.
They can do a lot to be honest.
They can be. How did you use QCLI?
I did an internship with Amazon. So they were sort of.
Yeah. They were pushing it on everyone because like I guess they want to lay off a lot of people.
So they're like make our
agents better so we can replace you.
Well, yeah. And you're still sticking with it. Like it must
be pretty good. It is. It is to be honest. And if you could
sort of like some people trust it
to like build an entire project.
But they also ask it to commit. So to like sort of. Yeah.
Yeah. They use get. So it can do a lot of impressive things even if you're like.
Even that way. So I guess this is much closer to the
problem that we're trying to solve. Right. Absolutely.
Yeah. I see a lot of crossovers with this.
I wonder. Yeah. I'll look into. I'll sort of. I'll start a
deep research prompt right now for finding like a master
class on how to you know free on how to learn QCLI.
There is you don't need no master class to be honest. Like
you just talk to it like sort of. It's yeah. It's just
yeah. It was basically you can have
it teach you a little bit like this is.
Yeah. Obviously that's how I use there a lot of the times
as well. Like my coding isn't great at all. So I kind of.
Ask it and then I sort of review it code and we sort of
learned at the same time we learned
together and like it fucked up and I'm like.
Yeah. And it finds out why it fucked up and then I tell it
sometimes that you shouldn't be fucking up.
Fucking up. So it's you don't really you don't really need
any like coding or like any complex. I don't know.
I didn't really. I meant like like metaphorically master
class. Oh yeah. Okay. My. I'm just going to ask like Google
Gemini to pull an assortment of like intro articles.
Coding agents or I'm coding agents I guess right in general
though. Oh yeah. Yeah because there's cursor there. Sorry.
Yeah there's cursor and you can sort of load up any model
there. I think if you I guess if you want to familiarize
yourself with something that's more.
I don't know broad. You might want to learn cursor. Right.
I'll give that a shot. I feel like right now I use.
I right now I use a visual studio code with get hub
co-pilot. Yeah. Yeah. I've even used the root plug in the S
code to import custom models using LM studio.
Which which plug in sorry. I'll go live on.
I can share my desktop screen. It's
a plugin called Roo R.O.O. And okay.
And now I forgot how you set it up. Oh
it looks like you could do cloud agents.
I forgot how I set it up but go to.
So they have MCP access but what I did was I somehow
connected it to this other application called LM studio.
Which is basically a way for you to download quantized
models and run them in your machine.
They somehow communicate if you if you upload you download
a model and you have the right specific
one loaded. I think only certain ones were.
Like when.
But.
Yeah. Yeah. I just had it connect there and I'm able to
interact with the code base. You can submit like.
Like shelf and stuff like that.
So it's.
But it's very available. It's very available. Yeah. It's
rudimentary too. I don't think it can. It's nearly as
capable of the stuff that you're
talking about. So but it's it's.
But it's available at a standalone
software. Or is it just extension.
I don't know. Yeah I'll check those things on a set. Yeah I
don't want to take up too much of your time as well.
Right. Yeah it seems like it can do.
Okay.
This is this looks like it's in the escrow.
Mm hmm.
Uh.
I'm gonna say.
Because if it's very subtle and you're already familiar
with it they might as well play around with it.
Like.
Yeah.
It gives you more flexibility. Yeah. Yeah.
Oh and.
I'll look into it.
It's.
So I found this one document.
That's.
This familiar to you it's
called the Amazon queue developer.
It's a.
Yeah.
I found.
So.
That's it right.
So there is Amazon queue developer. Yeah yeah that's it.
Yeah so there is a VSCode
extension as well which is I think.
Just referred to as queue dev I guess I'm not sure but then
there's the queue CLI which is the one that sort of is more
agentic like it's it's natively agentic.
So the other one they added the
agentic workflow afterwards like.
So you can sort of tell the
difference when you're running it from CLI.
There's a very subtle difference on
how they have access to workspaces.
That's sort of.
And also how they have access to your to your coding
environment as well that makes it's a difference.
You could try both and then
you'll you'll sort of understand.
Why one is better than the other.
But this I guess this is just for the queue developer which
is the backbone for for queue CLI as
well as the queue VSCode extension.
I see.
That's interesting.
I also found a mention that there's
this little sub note in that link.
Says that the queue CLI has become the key row.
So do you think is that like a new name for it or am I.
Misinterpreting what it's saying in the same document or
yeah yeah I just sent a link to it.
I looked up your CLI and.
It looked it looks pretty
similar to what you're talking about.
So I'm hoping yeah yeah yeah something like that but.
Let me see.
Sorry.
Here was the ally.
Interesting.
I've never heard of curious really.
I already had it installed from two months ago actually so.
Would be interesting if they.
But I'm still running it as Q.
So I mean that's that's strange.
Let me see if I can.
Let me see if I can find the
link that I used to install it.
Tell me.
OK.
Yeah OK yeah I'm using the same link
and it's taking me to this cure thing.
OK so it's just a rename.
Maybe I haven't.
I haven't tried this cure.
Because it looks like a separate thing as well like.
Like it has its own page and
everything but it's not what I'm running but.
I'll let you know.
Yes.
Yeah.
Yeah I'm gonna.
Oh do you want to go over like what was covered in the
meeting or anything like that.
I did.
You are good.
Yeah sorry.
Yeah please.
I'll just share with you the
agenda I generated from the transcript.
See.
Sorry not the agenda.
It was pretty good but we got
stuck on that document that I sent you.
Once we move past it we kind of just like
acknowledged the documentation all needs.
Organizational update.
We're going to kind of figure out
and fill our specific roles as a team.
Just by speaking about what we.
What kind of things we discover when the new teammates load
and run the repository for the first time.
Whether we come across any bugs when they do that because
you know once find on my machine when there's 10.
But.
You know who knows how good it's going to run on different
operating systems anything like that.
I don't know.
If I can find it here.
Oh I'm in the wrong.
I need to be on master.
Get back to the logs.
Here it is.
Yeah so this is a summary of the
transcript that I had generated.
It basically just goes over a lot of what we just went over
except you know for you you
had some more specific questions.
When it comes to the project planning I kind of just
acknowledge that we have a lot of documentation it's
scattered all over the place.
Also.
When it comes to this directory references at the bottom.
There's also like.
Some blind spots that we all kind of had.
It really just about like technical complexity.
Of the mathematic proposals for
the contextual integrity score.
I think I already.
Over that.
Okay.
Samuel also.
So Samuel he.
I don't know if you've looked into him.
I think I can share his LinkedIn.
Oh I have a list of. I have a list of the team LinkedIn. Let me share that with you too.
That's a good resource.
Samuel brought up.
The.
Fact that.
Wait a second.
Yeah we need a reusable benchmark.
I think you brought that up to you right.
So here's.
The. The. The. The.
The. The. The. Yeah.
So here's.
Is everybody.
Yeah I shared this with.
Somebody else ahead of the meeting.
Yeah, so the action items at the bottom,
they kind of just tackle what we agreed to do.
Everybody's going to install the dependencies.
Familiarize themselves with the project structure, test out
the project, try and get it running.
And then there's the end vision
that we have to talk about too.
Yeah, because I think we have a lot
of strong logic, but we don't have an
envision of what it's going to look like.
So that's a tough hurdle, I'll be honest.
You know, I've never really done anything
like this before. I just have this really
ambitious idea that I've been working on for months. But
we'll figure it out, we'll adapt.
If you happen to know anybody
who is pretty proficient in math,
that would be a huge plus. I'm going to reach out to some
professors and see if they can find
anybody that would be willing to help us
on this. Because as much as I want to trust
prompting and doing AI-generated research to kind of revise
all the mathematical logic behind it,
I need a human to look at it. Because it's a wave of my
understanding. It apparently has something
to do with vector embeddings and graph theory. And yeah,
it's up there. But I think the
implementation itself should be relatively simple once we
kind of reach a conclusion on that.
I'll try to have a think. And if
someone comes to mind, I'll let you know.
That would be a huge plus. No
pressure, though. Just if anybody happens.
Yeah, I would have suggested my
supervisors, but they're quite shit. To be honest,
they're barely doing their
jobs. I don't think they would be.
I don't think they would. What do they specialize in?
One of them specialized in computer vision. The other is
specialized in fairness in AI,
which is sort of a vague term for ethics-washing shit. Why
am I saying this? It is what it is,
I guess. That's sort of what the
field is becoming into, to be honest.
Really? Yeah, yeah. To slippery slope.
That's crazy. Excuse me.
I'm trying to think of anything else that
I've covered. If you haven't checked out
the website that's not the one that's public, but somebody,
I think it was Samuel, he created a
website in the onboarding folder that you can find in the
new folder. I'll send you a file path
to that. So if you pull the master branch, you can go to
this file path, open it in your browser,
and it gives you a good navigate. It's just a good link to
have. I'm building off of that today,
so I'm going to build file trees, and I'm going to
incorporate that into this kind of website.
Then what I'm going to do is I'm going to optimize the
documentation in the way that the files are
organized so that everything is much more understandable.
There's no confusing documentation
that pulls you away from the main plans. What I'm going to
do is I'm going to consolidate the plans
into a more rigorous planning document
than the most recent one, which was made
over a week ago, so it's time for an update. Then I think
after that, we'll be able to look at that
plan and incorporate the Envision into that and see where
everything fits in, especially in regards
to your questions about all those specifics. I'm hoping we
have enough of a foundation where
that kind of stuff can just easily fall into place, while
we can keep in mind all of the
documentation on how the competition is structured and what
the judges would be expecting to.
So it should just be a good balance between research and
discovery, active foundational plans,
and judge expectations. That should be the golden triad for
our next week here. I'm going to do my
best to make sure that the organization is good enough for
people to easily understand that
and contribute to it. I hope that's helpful.
Yeah, and I think you're doing a good job, honestly.
Yeah, in terms of organization.
It's getting there. It's kind of all over the place right
now, but at least everything's in
an appropriate folder so far, and everything is a
timestamp. We haven't accumulated too
much contextual debt, although we have accumulated some.
There's always going to be that.
It's just something. But yeah, I don't know. I've kind of
felt a lot of imposter syndrome about this
because I don't even have a college degree or anything like
that. It's been a little bit scary
this past week preparing to have people that are writing
PhD dissertations and stuff and take a
look at this project. Part of being
expected to be like, "You're crazy. There's no
coherent thought in this repository. It's just a bunch of
mumbo-jumbo." But I think I've hopefully
kind of phased past that. I don't know if you've looked at
the branch history of this repository,
but it started out as a
note-taking app. So it's come a long way.
It's come a long way. I don't want to keep you for too
long. It's been about an hour, but
yeah. No, I'm okay. You probably
want to go sleep as well at this point.
Honestly losing a little bit. But hey, I'm glad we'll catch
up. I would really appreciate it if you
connected with Garrett and kind of just reached out to him,
either in the server or gave him the
DM or something. Yeah. Because yeah, who knows where he's
in Germany, but that would be really
clutch if you guys could meet at the same time and kind of
see if you guys would be a good pair.
Yeah. Because we talked about the way that we're doing this. We're doing this in Germany. Yeah. Yeah. Because we talked about meeting asynchronously.
It's going to be difficult to
get everybody to meet at the same time. There's somebody in
Singapore. There's somebody in each
time zone in the US. But yeah, I just want
to say, yeah, thanks for meeting with me.
Yeah. Check out the index webpage when you have time. And
yeah, I'll be adding on to that.
Awesome. And also don't try to give me
some action points. Actually, that'd be
better for me. Like if you
could be like, do this and do that.
Sweet. So yeah, honestly, the questions that you asked me,
I think it would be really good if you
could come up with some big picture ideas, you know, from a
bird's eye view. You don't have to
get into the details. But if you could figure out what the
judges are going to be expecting from
this competition and try to come up with a
general, just a general idea of the kind of
submission structure and evaluation. Yeah. So, you know,
you can take a look at the A2A protocol
that they use. I don't know if Auth0, you know, that
company that has a sponsorship, we're going
to, I don't know if that's going to have anything to do
with it. That would be extremely helpful.
Also, if you could just, I'm going to
take your questions that you already sent me,
but if you have any more, feel free to just keep popping
questions into the questions channel,
because we need to figure out what we don't know right now.
It's important to ask those questions.
But yeah, if you could just try and, you know, take a look
at the code, come up with some like,
you know, high level answers and then put into the ideas
channel for now. So, you know, just really
casual for now. And then we can start to create some proper
documentation structure for this
and figure out like a planning and corporation pipeline,
right? Because there's this pattern
that we're going to constantly undergo. We're going to have
a plan, a planning document that
overscores like the large scope of the plan. We'll probably
create individual planning documents
from that. And at the same time, we'll probably have a
pipeline of all these questions and ideas
that we need to feed into the plan and revise accordingly.
So that's something that I'm going
to try and help figure out too. But if you have any ideas
of like that specifically, how the
planning aspect of this project could be better improved,
anything at all, that would be helpful
too. I'm not expecting you to do that, but if you have any
ideas for that. Yeah, I'll keep that in
mind. So there's that, there is a reach out to Ger as well.
And then I'll try to find someone
that might be able to help us with the math. I'll have a
look at the documents on me as well.
Thank you so much. And yeah, no worries. I'm not like, I'm
not going to over expect anything
from you, but I just, you know, I appreciate your effort
and I'm really happy that you were able to
join the team. I just, yeah, I'm
really grateful. Yeah, I'm happy to be here.
Sweet man. All right. Well, I'm going to let you go on and
yeah, just we'll catch up later. Hopefully,
I don't know, we'll figure out we're still working on call
scheduling and all that. But yeah,
I'll see you in the dashboard chat and stuff. And I'll let
you know if I have any updates.
All right. Sounds good. Take care. Bye-bye.