Great. Hi, everyone. Thanks a lot for joining this info
session for Agent X, Agent B's competition
in conjunction with the Agencies AI MOOC, the Massive Open
Online Course. Thanks, everyone, for joining.
Yes, my name is Dong Song. I'm a professor in computer
science at UC Berkeley and also a co-director
of a campus-wide center, Berkeley Center for Responsible
Decentralized Intelligence, RDI.
And RDI is hosting both the Agent AI
MOOC and also this Agent B's competition.
Next slide. So first, we'll give some quick overview of why
we are doing this competition,
and then we'll go into more details about what you need to
do for the competition and the more
information and so on. So first, the competition focuses on
agent evaluation. So first, what is
evaluation for AI models and agents? So these evaluations
are essentially systematic and
repeatable measurements built using these benchmarks that
provides a structured way to measure
different aspects for models and agents. This includes
different types of capabilities,
as well as risk assessment as well. Next slide. So why are
we doing a competition on agent
evaluation? Because actually, agent evaluation is really
important. Agent evaluation is important
for a number of reasons. It provides important measurements
for across models and agents for
both capabilities and risk assessments. And it guides safe
and effective development as well as
deployment decisions and helps expose both
weaknesses and strengths and help compare
different models and agents as well to help make the best
decision in terms of how to both improve
models and agents as well as how to choose the best model
and agents to deploy for real world
applications as well. And hence, reliable and high quality
evaluation of models and agents is critical
for develop and deploy effective and safe agents in real
world applications. And also,
a really important part about evaluation is that
evaluations essentially help set
the goalposts for the community for developing better AI
models and agents. There's a saying,
you can only improve what you can measure. And essentially,
AI's revolution is upper bounded by
evaluation. And also, right, we have seen
essentially the history of AI development
essentially has been marked by the different types of
evaluations and so on. So one thing I want to
mention here is so far, actually, when you look at the
community, most of the evaluation has been
focused on the model evaluation. However, as we develop
agents, just evaluation that just focus
on at the model level is insufficient. So essentially, we
need to transition from model
evaluation to agent evaluation as we now move to develop
agents and also to perform evaluations
for agents. So there are a number of key differences
between model evaluations and
agent evaluations. So for models, for example, in these
large language models, they are static,
and they can be right. They are oftentimes just text to
text and they can be multimodal as well.
But in general, these model evaluations focuses on just
providing prompt input and evaluates the
outputs of the model. And it's relatively, in this case,
it's relatively straightforward to do the
evaluation given the benchmark. But however, when we look
at agent evaluation, it's much more complex.
As we have discussed in the Agented AI MOOC, agents, the
overall Agented AI system can be
very complex. They do use the model as key components to,
and then they use the model to do
there's planning to use and reasoning and so on. And also,
Agented AI systems have memory storage
as well. And agents operate in
dynamic environments. And all these factors
essentially require more complex evaluations when we do
agent evaluation than just a simple model
evaluation. Next slide. So now, since as I mentioned, most
previous approaches actually focus
on model evaluation. And as agent benchmarks have been
developed, actually most of the existing agent
benchmarks still carry the same paradigm
that they are actually these evaluations,
are an eccentric design and with fixed harnesses. So
essentially, most of today's agent benchmarks,
I would say they have the wrong separation points where
they actually combine the benchmark with
fixed harnesses and only expose the
model, the interface between the model and the
agent benchmark. And hence, in this case, one can easily
evaluate with the same fixed harness
the benchmark evaluation across different
models, but it's actually very difficult
when you want to evaluate different agents with different
harnesses. And hence, in this case,
one want to evaluate a new agent on today's existing agent
benchmarks, and there's a high
integration overhead. One has to figure out for each new
agent how to do the integration with
the current agent benchmarks. And also this causes an issue
with the test protection mismatch.
Where one has to often change the production agents to
adapt to the testing benchmark.
So you actually may not be able to actually evaluate the
production agents as is. Next slide, please.
So these are some examples of the key limitations of
existing agent benchmarks. As you can see,
in order to evaluate agents with
different benchmarks, if you have m benchmarks,
oftentimes you have to do m integration, adaptation to
integrate and adapt this agent
to the m different benchmarks. And if you have n different
agents, essentially you have this
multiplication m by m, the
integration efforts. Next slide, please.
So this motivated us to develop a new paradigm that we call
a gentrified agent assessments,
AAA. And this serves as a new paradigm for open,
reproducible, and standardized agent evaluation.
And in particular, the key point of a gentified agent
assessments paradigm is that we enable what
we call a gentified evaluation, where the benchmark
evaluation itself, the assessor,
is actually an agent itself. And this assessor agents will
then directly communicate with the
assessee agents, the agents that actually need to be
evaluated through standardized protocols,
such as A2A. And also we use MCP, the standard protocol for
two use in this new paradigm as well.
So using this approach, we enable standardization and
utilizing the existing standards such as A2A
and MCP. And also we enable reproducibility
by utilizing an assessment control protocol
that controls for the setup and the
environments for the agent evaluation.
And in this case, one way to think about this is this new
gentified agent assessment paradigm
enables the key separation and the right interface
separation between the evaluation
benchmark and the agents. So with this approach, it's very
easy to bring your existing agents
and then to just be evaluated by the assessor agents that
we actually call green agents in the
competition. And the assessee agents, the currency that we
call the purple agents in the
in-agent beats competition. So again, this enables the
assessee agent to easily run, be evaluated.
And also this enables different harnesses and different
models easily to be evaluated.
And when compared to traditional agent benchmarking, this
gentified agent assessment paradigm
has a number of advantages. In a traditional agent
benchmarking, it's again primarily focused on
LMs with fixed harnesses, whereas with the AAA paradigm,
any agent conforming to the A2A protocol
can be evaluated by the assessor agent. And in the
traditional agent benchmarking, it provides
benchmark specific implementation dependent interface,
whereas in the AAA paradigm, it provides
standardized A2A interface for test
management and MCP for two use and to access.
And in the traditional agent benchmarking, it's prone to
test production mismatch, as I mentioned
earlier, and as many use for reference, whereas in the AAA
paradigm, it directly reflects
production level performance using this evaluation
paradigm. And for multi-agent assessments,
in the traditional agent benchmarking, it's actually very
difficult and requires bespoke
integration, whereas the AAA method natively supports
multi-agent assessments through
standardized interfaces and platform level
coordination. So it's actually provided and
enabled natively. And so these are the advantages and the
motivation for providing this new paradigm
of identified agent assessments. And in addition to this
paradigm and the issues addressed by this
new paradigm, there are also additional obstacles for
building impactful agent evaluation.
The overall system implementation can be
complex, requiring integrating of multiple LMs,
navigate diverse agent frameworks, observability,
environment setup, and infrastructure for agent
deployment monitoring and leaderboard management. And also,
overall, there is a lack of openness and
there's a lot of fragmentation. Currently, there's no
unified platform that can transform
research prototypes into widely
accessible, reusable evaluations.
Xiaojian, are you starting?
Yes, sure.
So this essentially motivates our new open platform,
AgentBets, for open, standardized,
and reproducible agent evaluation and research assessments,
which Xiaojian will discuss more
details. Sure. So here, I'm very happy to introduce you to
our current ongoing effort for
doing this AgentBets platform. Essentially, it's a platform
compliant to the AAA standard that we
just mentioned. And the goal is to build, again, the
standardized open and also reproducible
platform that satisfies our previous assessment related
requirement. And for standardization,
in addition to using H1MCP, we'll also provide a unified
SDK as long as a consistent workflow
for managing agent assessment and also agent instantiation.
Also targeting openness, we plan
to use the platform for publishing public agent,
maintaining benchmark, and also provide a set of
hosted environments for open evaluation.
In terms of reproducibility, we support
new control protocol that allows the auto reset of the
environment and also allow the hosts to run
hosted runs of agents. And while the assessment is ongoing,
we also enable multi-level trace logging
for better observability. And the platform is easy to use.
Essentially, you can use one file to
instantiate a new agent. And also there will be both on
platform and self-hosted options, just in
case someone wants to host private computations. And to
just make the platform more extensible,
we also support rich integrations of different types of
agents, as well as different types of
scenarios. And below you can see a general workflow for how
agent-based SDK, as well as the
agent-based platform service, can simplify the overall
development and evaluation of agentic
systems. And the platform is targeting the use case for
evaluating the agents and also letting
different agents to compete on the comparable tasks. It
also encourages contributing new
environments and benchmarks, allow people to collaborate
using agents developed by others,
and also let the agent improve. We support mainly two types
of evaluation mode. One is the benchmarking
mode for a single agent. It's best for having a unified
scoring and leaderboard for a single
agent task. We also have an arena mode, which basically
means that you might have multiple
agents joining the same assessment. And based on the type
of the assessment, either it's one-on-one
or it's more of a multi-agent team fight style evaluation,
there might be different ways of
assigning score. And this is best for adversarial
multi-agent evaluation or collaborative conditions.
And just as a general concept walkthrough, any H2A
compatible agents would be also compatible to
the agent-based platform, as long as they support the basic
task fulfilling to using an optionally
memory and other component. There are in general like two
types of agent, the assessor agent and
the SSE agent as introduced earlier. And just for a quick
example, imagine that you have a chess game
between a GBT40 agent and also a GBT5 agent. Then these two
agents will be your SSE agent. Well,
the agent who actually judges the board will be your
assessor agent. And we organize the evaluation
in the format of assessment. Each assessment would be a
multi-agent procedure between one of
the assessor agent and the other agents. Each assessment
will reflect one or more matrix of all
the participating or SSE agents reflecting on their score
change on the leaderboard. And also,
the assessor agent is responsible for reporting the final
result to the platform in the end.
So the platform itself provides a basic feature of agent
registry for people to discover new agents.
It also provides the agent controller for the task state
management, as we'll be also introducing
later. It also provides a feature for assessment kickoff to
orchestrate the collaboration procedure
between different agents for getting the
assessment result. And there are also extensive
features and a way of using it for assessment tracing,
leaderboard, proxying the MCP calls for
access control, agent hosting, etc. And we'll be releasing
more details in the future blocks.
Thanks, Sian. So we welcome everyone in the community to
join this AsianX, AsianB's competition
in conjunction with the Agente KI MOOC.
And we are very honored and grateful to the
to have the sponsors provide. We have
over $1 million in prices and resources,
thanks to the different sponsors here.
And we hope that the community and the
participants can join the competition to both actually help
together build public goods for
agent evaluation and also be a
great learning experience for everyone.
And next slide. So now let's talk a
little bit about the detailed logistics
for the agent piece competition. So for
the competition, there will be two phases.
The first phase that is going on currently is to focus on
building the assessor agents,
also called the green agents here. So in
particular, for phase one, the participants
will be building these green agents that actually define
the assessments and automates the scoring.
And in particular here, we have several different tracks
and different contribution types.
So first, let's talk about the contribution type. So one
type is to actually port or identify and
extend an existing benchmark. So the goal here is to
transform an existing benchmark into a green
agent that actually runs end to end on agent beats. And on
the agent beats competition websites,
here you can also see more examples of benchmark ideas that
actually list out a number of
example existing benchmarks that you can go identify and
extend. So that's one contribution
type. Another contribution type is to create a new
benchmark. In this case, it's to design a brand
new assessment as a green agent with novel tasks,
environments, automation and scoring. And we in
particular welcome participants to
develop new assessments in diverse domains that
have sufficient difficulty levels and also are realistic.
In particular, for example, you can
take your model after your even daily workloads and so on
and develop these new assessments as
green agents to evaluate agent capabilities, in particular
in domains that you are familiar with.
And also we have a custom track, which we'll talk about in
a minute. So these are different
contribution types. And then we also welcome for each of
these types either for identifying
existing benchmarks or to create a new
benchmark. For each of these contribution types,
we welcome contributions across different very diverse
application domains. So these include
coding domains, web agents, computer use
agents, research agents, software testing,
and game agents. And in, for example, web 3, decentralized
finance, cybersecurity agents,
healthcare, finance, legal domain, and in general, for
agent safety and agent security and multi
agent evaluation, and also many other domains, which I
won't be able to exhaust this here.
So again, we welcome the participants to consider these
different domains. So pick a domain that
you are interested in and also ideally you are familiar
with. And so the registration
phase has started. So for all the participants, you need to
both register individually as a
participant and also the team signup has opened as well. So
we welcome you to form teams and do
the team signup as well. Next slide. So that's phase one
for developing the green agent, which
is the accessory agents. And this will run until end of
this year. And then after phase one, we'll
enter phase two in early spring next year. And phase two
focuses on developing the purple agent,
which is the accessory agent. So in particular, after phase
one, we'll select the top green
agents from phase one and have participants to compete on
the public leaderboard for the
selected top green agents from phase one. And can you go
back? So I'll also talk about the custom
tracks. So in particular here, currently we have two main
custom tracks. So in general, as I
mentioned in the previous slides, you are welcome to
develop green agents in different domains.
And in particular, thanks to the sponsors, we also have
particularly two custom tracks, if you are
interested in these two specific areas. So one is our agent
security developing, essentially,
benchmark evaluation for right teaming and automated
security testing. And this track
is sponsored by Lambda. And more details will be announced
soon. And the second current custom track
is to extend the talk to bench. This is sponsored by
Sierra. And you can again go to the website
to look at the the detailed information about total bench.
And also more details about this
custom track will be announced soon as well. Please stay
tuned. And thanks to our sponsors.
There's very rich resources and also prices provided by the
sponsors to the participants.
So for every participant, you can look at the resources
available here. So essentially,
every participant actually just by participating in the
competition, you can get close to $500,
at least worth of credits for just participating in the
competition. And we also have various prices
for the winners of the competition provided by the
different sponsors. And more resources and
prices will also be announced later as well. Next slide,
please. And also please check the
competition websites for more details on
the key dates. And we, yes, we hope everyone
have a great time enjoying first for the first one,
building the green agents, the assessor
agents. And also we have the discord. We welcome everyone
to join the discord. So if you have more
questions about the competition and agent beats and so on,
please post your questions in the discord
as well. Thank you.
Shall I? Okay, cool. So I guess for the
next part, I'll be walking through some of the
implementation details on how to use agent beats or
interpret agent beats for agent evaluation.
These have like two parts. The first part,
I'll be showing how in general we can make,
we can identify an existing benchmark by
trying to trying to customize this interface
and standardizing it towards like a two way. And for the
second part, I'll be talking about how
for a standardized like a two way or identify the
assessment, how we can integrate it with agent
beats to make it an object that can be used in a general
agent assessment in the collaborative way.
So first, there are general three steps for identifying
this benchmark. Oh, by the way,
feel free to scan the QR code here or go to the official
website to read more about in general
this example. So the first step for identifying an
assessment is to try to sort out the interface.
And there are two general principles that can be applied
here. The first one, in general,
just by the definition of the task, humans should be able
to also solve whatever is presented to the
agent and like for with the given information. And under
the assumption that is human solvable,
in general is recommended to make the
solving procedure as agent friendly as possible,
just so that the agent can solve it easily. And in general,
achieve more reasonable score.
Imagine that if you can make a question
to be a multi twice problem, do not make it
slot fielding or tax generation problem. And that might in
general, make the assessment more
compatible. And the general example for how to exam this or
how to practice these principles
include, for example, you know, web browsing agent, you
might have the option to provide
your SSC agent the URLs to access those web page, or you
can follow the same paradigm as,
say, the current days, like in browser gene, you provide a
bunch of tools for navigating through
the web page and get the standardized response. And in this
case, since in general, human would
prefer the URL version since you can just open it with your
customized browser and use your own
sort of way of like opening a website, then it's actually
recommended to organize it so that
your web browsing task is actually providing a URL rather
than just translating things into two
actions. And similarly, for coding agents, there's a
difference of providing a coding
environment versus if you just provide a repo to be changed
and expect the agents to write you the
patches. And in general, if you compare to the like the
human related assessment, just imagine
the first scenario to be you share your laptop with, let's
say like given SSE versus you just
provide a public GitHub repo link, and then just ask others
to do PR. In this case, I think too,
if you want to examine the agent's ability to interact
with, say, the code editor, then the
first way is preferred. Otherwise, the second way might be
more cleanly handled. And a recommended
way to sort out the interface would be
try to read the original paper if you are
migrating from an existing benchmark, or just think about a
task formulation for the new types
of benchmark. And in general, it's also recommended to read
the code base if you are migrating from
existing benchmark, and think about how to actually deliver
the same piece of information,
but within the A2A format with minimum code intrusion as
possible. So here we actually
provide example of using Talbench. And as you can probably
see the figure from the Talbench
paper actually clearly presents like what would be the
general interaction structure. And if you
go into the their code base, you will see that there is
this very clear interface of environment
and agent that you can extract. And what as long as you can
separate from this layer, it is possible
to actually make it A2A compatible. And
specifically for this Talbench example, there
remains like two key challenges for identifying it and
standardizing it with A2A. So the first is that
you will have a cross-agent two-use scenario. So first of
all, the Talbench is just for the context,
the Talbench is a two-use benchmark that the assessor will
have a bunch of tools, and the
assessor will be trying to use these tools to solve like
let's say a given problem. And in this
scenario, since we're identifying it and the assessor is
actually a separate, a different
agent from the assessor, you should figure out a way to
actually pass the two leads from the assessor
to the assessor just to make sure that the assessor can
respond in the expected format.
And in the original repl, the tool is directly provided to
the chat completion interface.
So there's, it actually doesn't need any sort of
separation. But since now we want to make this
compatible and standardized so that everyone can run this
evaluation, we need to think about how
we can pass these two leads from the assessor to assessee.
And there are in general three ways.
The first way being the simplest that you just expect a
participating assessee agent to have
the knowledge about these tools, and then just operate
based on this given format. However,
this actually defeats our purpose of identifying the
assessment and also is less standardized.
And the second way is to try to ask the assessor to explain
the two access requests to the white
agent and then ask for what two names that the assessor
want to call. So, well, this is achievable.
And also this is the way we use in our example. One of the
potential problem is that this cannot
leverage the agent internal tool call mechanism. Say, if
you have a hyper planning or organization
or some sort of harness regarding the two selection, then
this part cannot be properly evaluated.
There's also a third way of doing this, which is to ask the
green agent or the assessor agent to
provide an MCP server for accessing the tool and then just
get the connection or get the URL to the
assessee agent. And while this being the most general
approach, there will be some coding complexity
and also this requires a dynamic discovery ability of the
assessee agent. So, there are trade-offs.
And also, the second challenge is at where
you migrate the evaluation. The tool trace
might not be directly visible to your
assessor agent, thus grading can be problematic.
And in general, to just make sure that you have a rather
independent identified assessment,
there can be three parts. So first, you want to build the
green agent or the assessor agent and
the assessee agent or the white or the different like
participant in this multi-agent procedure.
And also, you would like a kickoff script, which sends a
message to the assessor agent to kick off
the whole procedure. And later within the agent's platform,
this can be simplified by having a
platform on the component to send this message. But just
for a complete example, you might want
to have this separate component. So, implementation-wise,
you would like a kickoff script that
looks like the following. So, you will try to send out this
kickoff message to the green agent,
and that's it. And then for implementing the green agent,
what you need to essentially do is to
implement an agent interface. And in this case, a
coding-based workflow would help, would actually
solve the problem that it just loads the corresponding
environment and then issue and simulate the
conversation with the assessee agent. And it might be
slightly different for MCP-based implementation
since you need to set up the separate MCP server, but the
general workflow remains the same.
And similarly, you will have a participant agent that can
be very simple, as simple as like just a
general agent, since they are the candidate to be tested.
And again, here, the purpose is that for
any agent, under any agent harness, you
can incorporate it in a standardized test.
So, once you have identified the
assessment and standardized your
agent interface, the next step is to leverage the
agent-based platform or the agent-based format
to make it reproducible. And there are also some
potentially helpful materials that may help you
with this overall development procedure.
So, for the second part regarding how to
integrate your each agent with the agent-based. So, now you
have the identified assessment and also
having the baseline agent and the launcher.
The integration just takes three steps. So,
the first step is to wrap your agent with what we call the
agent-based controller, which will be
also discussed a little bit later. And the second is to
deploy your agent to the cloud,
to some sort of cloud platform to obtain a public IP as
well as protected by PPLS. And at the last
step is to connect it to the agent-based platform so that
actors can actually leverage it for a
multi-agent assessment. So, for agent-based controller,
it's actually a lightweight component
that can help you manage your agent instance. It has
several key responsibilities. The first
actually exposes a service API for managing your agent
state. For example, for attracting the agent
live needs, restarting the agent, or checking the agent
log. It also detects and starts or
restarts your agent based on the API request. And
additionally, just for the purpose of maintaining,
making it friendly to a microservice architecture, you also
have a feature to a proxy order request
that is sent to the internal agent instance. And just for
human friendly, UI also provides a
management panel for both debugging and also checking the
internal status. And the reason
you need such a component is that other users can actually
test your agent result manually
restart your agent between runs or just reach out to you to
say your agent needs some state
reset. So the procedure is also simple. You install the
package, you set up an executable
named run.sh, which in general tells the system how you
would start your agent and also make that
script executable. And then you run the
controller from the package. And what you get
is that you will have first a local management page for
monitoring the agent status. You also
have a proxy URL for accessing your agent similar to the
one that is starting your local host.
And also, you will have you can test whether this is set up
by just checking the agent card.
And here is an example for what you will see if you're
using this controller. So essentially,
you will try to manage your agent instance
internally. And there's also like a ongoing
like scaling feature that might help you manage multiple
agent instance in the future.
And you can toggle reset just from a controller API. So
once you have this controller,
you might consider like deploy your agent with a public IP
and POS. And there are also like in
general, a few steps for deployment. Including like
provision of yam also installed a program
getting a certificate and for more than alternative. We like you might want to contain a
containerize your agent and potentially with some sort of
field packs or Docker file and also
deployed for a micro service or function plugin sort of
like service just for getting that
TLS and also like auto scaling automatically. So the steps
are also quite simple. Here's an example.
So for example, you can set up the profile and then just build with a few packs and then push
it to a Docker registry. And the benefit is that you don't
need to manually set up the HTTPS anymore.
And also the management of your agent. So the last step is
to actually publish your agents
on the agent based platform. And once
your agent is public accessible, others can
discover it and also including it in general assessment. And the procedure is also simple
within the website, in the form. And then the key
information you need to provide here is the
controller URL that you set up earlier with public IP. And
for a complete example, coding example of
what you need to change from identifying the assessment to
agent based integrated agent,
please feel free to take a look at this
code patch. And so once you have this set
up, you also have next step of writing an
assessment and viewing the result from the
agent based dashboard. And we also have some announced the
feature for hosting agent etc,
just to sort of like signify the workflow.
But in general, that would be the flow for
integrating with the agent for agents. Thank you.
Okay, yes, so now I can continue. So
let me actually let me share screen.
Oh, I just did.
If you would like to. Okay, I think it's easier. So instead
of I have to say next slide, I'll just,
I think it may be easier. Right.
Okay, so people can see right. Okay, great. Okay, so yeah,
thanks, everyone. So now you've
understood the motivation for this new paradigm for
evaluation, the identified agent assessments,
and also understand, have seen some examples of how to
build the assessor agent, the green agent.
So now, we'll also talk a little
bit about further competition, how the
how the submissions will be
evaluated. And so first, let's look at,
given that we are talking about agent evaluation, then
first, let's look at what is a good
evaluation system. So one key
question is, as we develop agent evaluation,
how do we make sure that it's a high quality? And there are
many different aspects to ensure
high quality evaluations. And so, as I mentioned earlier,
so you want the evaluation to have
actually to be to be challenging
enough, so that you can actually differentiate
strong models, weak models, strong agents versus weak
agents. And also we want the evaluation to
be realistic. Ideally, the evaluation is more mounted after
real world, you know, useful tasks,
and real world settings and, and so on. And also, the
evaluation, we hope that it can actually give
a fairly accurate assessment, and with
like, no bias or low bias, and so on. So,
so there are many different aspects that
one actually needs to pay attention to.
So in particular here, as one example of important aspects,
is that you want to make sure that,
as I mentioned, the evaluation, for example, your scoring
function, is actually high quality,
it gives the correct evaluation. So outcome validity is
very important for making a good evaluation.
And so given that they, depending on the different tasks,
they, there may be, you know, different
outputs. And this will require different ways to judge the
results. So depending on the tasks that
you are developing, then you will need to develop
appropriate methods, especially if you are building
a new benchmark assessment, you need to develop appropriate
judging methods. So this oftentimes
depends on the different types of the outputs that you need
to evaluate over. For example, for
text outputs, some may do stream matching. And there are
different things you need to be careful
if you are doing, for example, sub-stream matching. And
sometimes one may do LMS as a judge. However,
in general, it's really important to ensure that when LMS
is used as a judge, it actually does
provide high accuracy in the evaluation. And in general,
especially for this competition,
we do encourage participants to try to provide as much
ground truth, or rigorous rubrics
for the evaluation as possible, instead of using as a
judge, which oftentimes does not provide
high enough accuracy, depending on the tasks. So again,
outcome validity is a very important
aspect for evaluating your green agents.
So here, this is also another example for
if you are judging code generation, then
you can use different methods, including
unit testing or end-to-end testing, fast testing, and so
on. And you can also provide evaluation
based on environment state changes for a lot of task
environments. This actually can provide
a very good method for judging the outcome validity. For
example, it includes ground truth,
and that actually includes all states achievable after
success, and the check for relevant and
irrelevant states. And in general, so this
is in this case, providing good ground truth
based on environment state challenges and
state changes can be a very effective way
of performing high quality assessments.
And here are some examples to consider
for judging multi-step reasoning, depending
on the matching quality measures and so on.
And also, as you build these assessments, our green agents,
it's important to pay attention to
the different ways how the evaluation could go wrong. In
fact, building high-quality evaluation
can be very challenging. There are many different ways
things can go wrong. So for example, the data
can be noisy or biased. There can be data continuation
issues in the sense that maybe
somehow the model agents, if I'm using some existing tests,
the model may have already seen
the tests in training data, then
this can cause data contamination. And
also with agents, sometimes there can be shortcuts, in
which case the evaluation can be gamed.
You'll be surprised how smart these agents
can be, that can try to take shortcuts to
to gain the evaluation. And also, as I
mentioned, ideally the assessment benchmark
should be challenging enough. And also,
in particular, you want to build these
evaluations that are sufficiently challenging, not just for
today's models and agents, but also
for you want the evaluation to have sufficiently long shelf
life, so that it can still remain
relevant even in the coming near terms and even longer
terms as well. And also, ideally,
these evaluations should focus on high-impact tasks
environments and be realistic and practical.
And here, I want to briefly mention a few case studies of
some examples of good evaluation systems.
And again, so when you are considering what to build for
the assessor agents or the green
agent, there are a number of questions to consider. In
particular, what is a good benchmark
and how to construct it? You need to select the initial
goals. What is the goal and what
essentially what do you want to evaluate? What are the
tasks and what are the environments to run the
agent to achieve the goal? And how to build the data
collection pipeline, how to evaluate
the assessor agent. And again, you want
to prioritize real-world realistic tasks,
have sufficient difficulty levels, and
actually have different difficulty levels,
and now easy to get contaminated or saturated. Here are
some examples that I just want to briefly
mention. So, CyberGem is actually our recent work as a
benchmark to evaluate AI capabilities in
cybersecurity, in particular for evaluating agent
capabilities in identifying vulnerabilities,
both previous and normal vulnerabilities, as well as
previously unknown vulnerabilities, and also
generating what's called a POC, proof of concepts. These
are inputs that actually trigger vulnerability.
And CyberGem actually was started with the goal to be
realistic, and in particular, actually it
contains close to 200 large-scale widely distributed
real-world open source software
that contains over 1500 previously known
vulnerabilities. And CyberGem is constructed
using well-constructed environments that are continually
licensed sandboxes to run these programs. And CyberGem
actually has, as a benchmark,
has demonstrated that the AI capabilities in cybersecurity
has been improving really fast,
and also has been included in Anthrappix
system cards for its latest model release,
CERN 9.5, for evaluation of AI capabilities in
cybersecurity. And you can find out more
information about CyberGem and how it's constructed on the
CyberGem website and in the paper.
And as an example, in the paper it actually performs data
contamination analysis to show that
there is minimum data contamination issues
that need to be concerned in this benchmark.
And also, CyberGem construction focuses on
high-quality evaluation that actually has
high-quality ground truth built into the evaluation through
the use of runtime sandhazers,
which actually gives ground truth and
results to show that whether the construct is
input is an actual POC that triggers vulnerability and also
separates whether it triggers a previous known
vulnerability versus a new vulnerability.
So that's the CyberGem. Here's another example for
TalBench, which actually Xiaoyuan just
did a walkthrough in terms of how to
identify TalBench as an accessory agent.
And so again, yeah, welcome to look at the details of
TalBench in the TalBench paper,
as well as the open source
benchmark. As an example, TalBench provides
a very good example benchmark for
computer use agents that actually covers a fairly
diverse different types of
environments for different types of tasks.
And again, you can give the interest of time. We won't go
through the details. You are welcome
to go into detail to look at the construction of TalBench
and how it is evaluated, where it
actually provides different metrics for evaluation as well.
And I also wanted to quickly mention the
TalBench, which is a next generation from TalBench, which
includes more dynamic interaction
between users and agents. And also, as I
mentioned earlier, we have a custom track
for TalBench. And again, you can look
at the TalBench paper and the open source
repo for more information. And then there are some other
examples that you can take a look
as well, such as the GTP well, and also CIM arena. So these
are all very interesting examples to
take a look. And then I want to just quickly conclude by
talking about then what are the
judging criteria that you need to consider
as you build these two different types of
assessor agents or green agents. As I mentioned, there are
two contribution types. One is to
integrate and identify existing benchmark.
The other one is to build a new benchmark.
So the first one is to integrate and identify existing
benchmark. On the competition websites,
there are links, again, as we showed earlier, that you can
look at example ideas for existing
benchmarks that you can identify and extend. And in
general, the workflow goes as the following.
So you want to identify the existing
benchmark that you are interested in extending and
identifying. And then you want to then essentially follow
the kind of steps that Xiaoya has mentioned
through his examples with the TalBench.
That you want to then identify the benchmark
and build the assessor agents by
following the similar steps as Xiaoya showed.
And also after that, we also strongly recommend you to even
though this existing benchmark,
a lot of the existing benchmarks, they do have quality
issues and so on. So we do strongly
recommend you to also investigate and do your own quality
analysis for the existing benchmark
that you selected. And when you encounter issues, to then
take the next step to ideally help correct
some of these issues and potentially even further expand
the existing benchmark as well.
So for the benchmark quality analysis, you can do it
through several different methods. You can do
it through manual validation to sample and check data
correctness, clarity and difficulty.
You can check the evaluator to confirm for metrics and also
the judges that actually do align with
the true task success and also analyze for bias and
contamination and other potential issues and
limitations as well. And then once you identify issues in
these existing benchmarks, you can try
to correct the benchmark if there are errors and also you
can try to expand the benchmark to
further improve its quality, size and diversity as you see
fit. And in terms of identifying issues
and correcting issues, so this is a very good example for
you to take a look. So there's the
original suite bench which provides a very good starting
point but had a number of issues and
later on with the suite bench verified, later on people
corrected, identified issues and corrected
them. And so now in general suite bench verified is
actually more widely used now for as the
evaluation for coding agents. So that's the first type for
extending, identifying existing benchmark.
As I mentioned, the second contribution type is to build
your own like new benchmarks.
And in particular, in this case, you want to identify
realistic tasks. You want to first
identify what task you want to and the environment that you
want to evaluate your benchmarks in.
And ideally you want to develop tasks that
actually reflect useful real world scenarios.
And it's even better if it's a domain that you are familiar
with and even tasks from your
regular workload and so on. And for the
evaluation, you can develop different methods
either with ground truth with the menu
developed ground truth or you can have some
semi automatic automatic methods as well.
And also, so now we are seeing more and more
multi-agents being developed as well. So we do encourage
you to build multi-agent benchmarks
as well. So here's a quick step
by step checklist for building your
associations of green agents. Make sure that
you choose the task you want to evaluate on
and design the environments that the agents are being
tested and need to run in. And this includes
providing the set of tools that the agents can interact
with, the agents that the agent can,
the actions the agent can take and also the environment
feedback to the agents after each action.
And also then design the metrics that your green agents
will evaluate with. For example,
in this booking ticket setting, the success rate for
booking tickets, how cheap the ticket is,
what the ticket satisfies the user's requirements and so
on. And then you need to design the task
cases to evaluate your green agent. You need to think about
the different scenarios of your purple
agents trying to complete the tasks and design the various
test cases to evaluate your green
agents that can handle the different test cases where
different purple agents will try to be
evaluated by the green agents. And also I want to mention
that in general top AI machine learning
conferences now have data sets, benchmark tracks. So for
example, this is the New York's, the top
deep learning conference, top AI conference for year 2025.
This will happen in December. And it's
a cover paper for data sets and benchmarks. So ICML also
has its data sets benchmark track
that's actually with the deadline in January. So if you
built your accessory green agents,
it also can be helpful that you can
consider the work later on you can submit the work
to these conferences as well. And
also we do plan to offer certain example
tasks and evaluations. So for people
who are interested, you can join as well
and potentially even co-author papers as well. So finally,
for judging criteria, when you are
building your accessory agent and green agents, there are a
number of aspects to keep in mind.
Later on we'll provide more details for the judging
criteria, but these are in general the different
aspects that you can keep in mind. So this is an example
list of different aspects for you to
consider for building new benchmarks for the judging
criteria. For example, Goa normality is your
benchmark important novel and covers new capability space.
And how is the scope and scale?
It's a benchmark large and diverse enough to give reliable
results, evaluate your quality,
matrix clear is your job, your evaluator
high quality and consistent. For validation,
did you perform manual checks or spot validation on the
evaluation outputs from your green agents?
For reliability, do your evaluation scripts and green
agents run robustly on agent beats
and quality assurance and your bias or
contamination checks that you have done.
And realism is a benchmark realistic, for example, with
real world workloads instead of
toy or unrealistic settings. And impact is a benchmark
reusable, well documented and presents
it clearly. And then similarly, there are similar aspects
for the judging criteria when you are
extending and identifying an existing
benchmark as well. So here, in addition to
successfully identifying the existing benchmark, you also
want to analyze for quality issues for
the original benchmark that you extended and try to find
whether it has any issues, flaws.
And for facefulness, is your implementation reproducing
results from the original benchmark
excludes excluding the flaws that you fixed? Quality
assurance is your implementation
correcting the flaws in the original
benchmark and expanding the courage
of the original benchmark. And
evaluator quality and validation, reliability,
and these are similar aspects that I mentioned in the
previous slide as well. And also impact is
your implementation reusable, well documented and presents
it clearly. So I think that's all.
So thanks everyone for joining this presentation. So now we
also open up for some Q&A and Xiong
will help answer questions as well. Xiong, can you just
take the questions and you can
start repeating the questions and then give the answers.
Sure, of course. So I go through, I guess
some of the questions that I previously, I guess I'll
probably just start from those. And well,
meantime, please feel free to send more questions in the
chat. So there was this question for
does this mean HWA and MCP need to be a part of agentic
flow in order for AAA to work?
Yeah, in general, the HWA is used for communicating single
phase as the interface we incorporate for
doing task management. And instead of
just setting up like a custom customized one,
like yet another standard, we're just
using HWA based on is like data format and
way of like managing tasks. And similarly, for to use,
since MCP is already sort of a common
protocol for everyone, we are just leveraging that for a
green agent to provide necessary tools for
agents to interact. And yeah, so
there's also a second question that
where's the assessor is coming for agent is coming from? Is
it available somewhere we need to be
written along with other agent? Yeah, great question. So
the assessor agent or the great
agent is actually the main deliverable for the first phase.
That means that so first of all is
equivalent to designing a new assessor
agent is essentially deciding a new benchmark.
But also like along with the
standardized interface and also like reproducible
sort of ability that so yes, like it
should be coming from I guess like the
submission for come as the submission for this competition.
And I'm also going to go through
some questions from other channel.
So there was this question of
you will not provide any API for white purple agent to use
for testing for testing it without
reagent. So we're not providing well, we are not providing
a standardized white agent is
currently like a most modern agent framework do have your
eight way support. And in general,
feel free to use those or like the off the shelf example as
the general great agent to test against
retargeting. In general, a good great agent, a good design
like assessor agent should be able
to be general enough to test any general assessor agent.
However, well, that being said,
we also recommend you to also build a better baseline
assessor agent separately just to
demonstrate that you're like like for certain improved
agent that your benchmark or your
your assessor agent can distinguish them and actually
measure the ability. For example,
if you're building a web browsing agent, a web browsing
environment for like a web browsing
green agent, then potentially you might want to use or
incorporate other like agents with
web browsing tools or with web browsing ability either from
a visual version or a text version,
or a visual input or text input to provide more baselines.
So there was also a question about the some current, I
would say that difficulty using the website.
Well, the there will be a so first of all, there will be a
different, actually, a different set of
UIs and the upgraded version of the website for the
official submission for this competition.
So I would personally recommend to start with the identify
example, or the like the top entry example
for identifying the benchmark first. And then in terms of
integration, we'll have like a new
blog coming really soon, perhaps like within a week to help
provide more information. Thanks.
Another question from chat, how long do
we expect the benchmark to be given that
maybe there's only limited budget? So great question.
So I'll start by I guess, like answering this part. So
essentially, I think like the size of
the benchmark is determined by two factors. So first, of
course, the budget and second is also
the question, the investigation scope. It's not always the
case that the benchmark is as large
as possible. I think as long as it is of a size that can
truly do like a correct management in a
rather stable format, and also sort of successfully support
your evaluation target, then that should
be fine. For example, just in general for like a web
browsing, like a web browsing benchmark,
depending on whether you are testing, say, a general web
browsing ability, or say, if you are
just testing for BI related like website, or for
commercial, or for like in the financial or
medical setting, sort of like website, depending on like
the problem for scope, I think as long as
the size of their site properly supports that scope, it
should be fine. And another question is
how the final assessment will be done as there are true
assessments based on green agent and
purple agent. So well, I guess like the standard will be
provided for two phase like more on our
official website. In general, those will be like assessed
as like different tracks and assessed
separately. Another question is, how can we extensively
test our green agent with LAM API
limitations? I see. So in terms of API limitations, so I'll
encourage to explore, first of all,
like different against like, platforms. And also in
general, this, I think this sort of go in line
with the previous question of the budget for creating a
benchmark that I think the purpose
is rather just a complete benchmark under the scope rather
than just, I would say like make
it as large or make it as like, necessarily repeat the
experiment, multiple times as more as possible.
So there are some like, I guess, like in general, public
resource for getting more API requests from
different, I guess, like LAM API provider. But in general,
just, I guess the principle here is
design the experiment more carefully.
And also just look out for more resource.
Another question from the chat that are we doing encourage
new benchmark or identifying existing
benchmark, I think there'll be measured as first of all,
just what we measured under different tracks.
So we in general, like encourage both of them as like both
of them will be significantly
contributing a rather standardized agent evaluation future.
And overall, the assessment will be made
based on both the effort and also
the final outcome for the benchmark.
Say for example, there are some like, currently there are
some like benchmarks that are
originally quite simple, but non standardized, can really
make them like really general,
really flexible for different types of like agent, and also
provide a, let's say like a logging
interface or some like helpful agent separation that could
potentially lead to very interesting
findings or very high utility, then those will be like also
significantly contribution and
counted in the in the in the general assessment. And also,
for new benchmark is the same story,
like it doesn't have to be marking the previous question,
it doesn't have to be super large.
And as long as it's like novel and satisfied, like most of
the criteria that is mentioned in the
earlier part of this info session, then you should be like
a good candidate for submission.
[no audio]
Okay, here's another question.
So why is the evaluator for the agent
won't it be just an LM evaluator, not LM agent?
Good question.
So actually one of the core part
for agent B's is that we are treating,
we are trying to unify the
abstraction here by also making the evaluator,
or what we call the assessor, an agent entity.
And in this way, they actually follow the
same set of interface as a general agent
based on A2A.
So you can actually manage
the, think of it as the following,
can manage the benchmark the same way
as you might manage agent themselves.
And that will actually simplify the system development as
well as just conceptually a lot.
And here, I'd want to note that
the evaluators or the assessors
is not necessarily driven by LM.
So they might be agent, but more
towards the, I guess, original concept of like
agents in reinforcement learning
that you would react to the environment,
which is also like the platform for
the request for evaluating other agent.
And it's not necessarily driven,
or at least for this assessor agent,
it's not necessarily driven by LM.
However, I also do want to
point out that most of the, well,
significant amount of recent agent
evaluation is based on LM as a charge,
which means that the LM component is
already somehow within the evaluation procedure.
And under this assumption, we are seeing that in the
future, more and more agents will be
judged by or evaluated by other agents.
And thus, we are making the concept or the
abstraction to be consistent at this stage.
And for the questions, please feel
free to leave them in the Discord channel,
which is the preferred channel. Thank you.
Oh, and for the second part of the earlier
question, yes, there will be LM evaluator,
and there will also be the evaluator
agents, so there are also evaluators.
Okay, so given the time reason,
thanks for the wonderful questions.
And while you're working on here, for more questions,
please feel free to leave them in
Discord and we'll be replying
in a synchronous manner later.
Thank you all again for joining
today's session and hope you had fun,
have fun in building your next agent evaluation. Thank you.