Hmm we don't
So yeah, she had that yesterday and
hopefully she's gonna start feeling better
Yeah called her a few minutes ago, but she didn't answer so
I'm hoping she's just sleeping or something
But yeah, I got I got a check-in with her pretty soon
Yeah
Brition you're the best
Oh, yeah
since you're looking up now that she's
been approved for the infusions because
She's been waiting for months for that and it it took like
I don't know it just took a long time to get things going
so
you
at that point
Awesome. Yeah, yeah
Yeah, and then like as for the
this for the whole logo mesh thing I finally managed to
Test some battles. I wrote some scripts
Yeah, like ransom battles with
different large language models
Because yeah, I was like I was looking at the the draft
Research paper that's written up
and I'm like, well, we need to provide
like evidence that
What we've built is like quantifiable proof that
That the theories in the paper may have potential
So what I did was like I used a
tiny model. I think I used a mistral
Language model and then I yeah, I
ran it with like three scenarios
45 times oh here
Hello
Happy new year to you. I laugh within me a new year. Yeah
Sorry for joining late. I am my camera on
the computer, but somehow I moved it somewhere
So I had to join in two places
on the screen and on the phone
So I'm here on both
Awesome
Thank you
Yeah, yeah
Thank you for arranging this meeting really appreciate
thank you for waiting for me as well
I was kind of just I just started
Talking about you know, let me share my screen here. Oh,
yes. And also could you send me the link for the paper?
You know
Okay
Okay, so
Yeah, let's go here
Okay, so let me get you that link
Okay, I'll just I'll put it in the
Google meet chat and then I'll send it to
You on discord
I'm remoting into my PC here. Hold on. Hold on
Maybe I can find if it's in the repository. Um
so
Yeah, I mean if you just go to the github website and you
go to the logo mesh repository
If you just type in the search bar
Which is
November 18th, 2025. That's that's when I dated the paper
Then you'll find it you'll find the most recent draft
Agent text submission paper
Yeah, no, it's I think it's I think it's contextual debt
paper copyright edition or some silly name like that
I didn't I didn't have the naming conventions
Down very well
2025 11
With a
one
Here it is and then I have the link here. So
Okay, awesome
Yep, got it
And then i'll try and find on google drive really quick
Oh
I don't actually think it
Oh, you know what this one's this
one's an outdated version of the papers so
Yeah, okay
Yeah, the the one that I have in
google drive doesn't include all of the math
Okay
Okay, here we go, okay
um
Yeah, so
Anyway, uh this version of the
paper includes um, I think it's
All the way down in
Yeah, it's called section three formalization the
contextual integrity score that's
where like the math is first introduced
And
There's kind of like
I don't know. There's kind of a suggested loop
Um, which I i'm 99 sure is what
i've translated into the actual arena
Which is good
And uh, and then basically like what i'm going to do is
like update the paper and include the results
of some tests by
kind of visualizing
A few database files
I have to I just realized
um
I just realized I accidentally
weighted the scores differently in one of the
One of the logs
So we'll have to manually
weight the score again, which
shouldn't be hard because it's
Like all of all the information
exists to do that so I can fix that
um, but I was kind of hoping for
Your guys is helping like visualizing the data that we did
collect because what I did do
was I ran
25 battles
in an in the agent arena with uh three scenarios
And I did that
Three times free per agent. I need to tell
my dog to be quiet. Hold on. I gotta mute
so you try different combinations
of agents for different tasks like or
Yeah, so
Hold on I'll I'll get you the file path for
the scenarios. I think it's just right here
Okay, judge no
Um
Hold on hold on these are for the red agent
Yeah, look I need I need like 15 seconds
Yeah, what I have to do is
according to what we're talking
about in this meeting I have to
Create a briefing document at the same time. So I just
finished doing all this last night
um
But from what I understand one of the scenarios is an email
validator. So it prompts the purple agent to
Um
Create
an email validation system
and
it does so in a way that asks for
Specific aspects of the code so that it can
evaluate those things with the cis metric
And what the green agent does is like after it prompts the
purple agent it waits for the output
And the output is delivered within a json string
And then what it does is
The green agent has four metrics. It has the three
contextual integrity score pillars
But then the fourth one is actually just
A simple llm as a judge. So whatever
whatever model is loaded into the arena
Like if mistral is loaded into the arena it will
Uh be used for the green agent. It'll be used for the
purple agent and if the red agent is turned on
Which it was not for these tests
because these tests were just for
the the contextual integrity score proof
Then yeah, so the green so the the fourth
metric is logic but let me see if I can find
So essentially, um
You ran how many models you said
just three
three models and three scenarios, so
I I was just wondering how we ended up with um
How many you said 20?
I don't know 40
right
20 25
25 battles. Yeah
battles per model just as an initial run
Uh-huh. So you're you're
re-running them with the same scenarios
Yeah, and I decided uh, I
decided to pick the scenarios at random
no
I
Just I don't know if that's that was I don't know if that
was the correct thing to do. So
Um, if possible, I can rerun
scenarios today if we don't want
If we don't want that but I just
selected that initially because
Um, I just didn't put enough thought into
Like whether or not I should do
You know like a rounds
a number of rounds that's divisible by three like I could
have done 30 rounds per agent and then just
done, you know 10 rounds of each scenario, but
I don't know. I was just I was just
trying to get things done yesterday
So I just went with whatever my
coding agent suggested and it was like okay
We'll just just select the rounds randomly and then do 25
each and I was like, okay,
whatever. We'll just go with that
um, but it should roughly amount to
We should still have enough
data that we need to visualize uh
the results
It takes it takes a a few hours to rerun everything
with the larger models
so I could do
I could rerun it today if you guys want but
My main concern is just basically
getting you guys the information
um
With dt. I was kind of like hoping
Uh, so the the round information the
results of the rounds, uh, everything was stored
in a uh, sqlite
Database, so I have okay. I have three separate databases
Mm-hmm, and i'll be
When I give you guys the briefing document from today's
meeting i'll make sure that the file paths are
um in this meeting
Okay, uh as for
The three scenarios, uh, they're all defined
Oh email the validator was skipped
Okay
Yeah, I might I might be running
some extra battles today. We'll see
but everything's defined in
Source screen logic tasks.py.
Let's take a look at that really quick
Going there source screen green logic. Yep
And then
Should be tasks.py
Task.py just okay. Yeah, so we
skipped over the email validator task
um because
I was running into
some dns lookup errors
because when the agent was being prompted to
Create the email validation function it was like
assuming that it was going to have access to the internet,
so I just I kept running into
To some network denialers. So I
I tried to fix it and then I just excluded
it because it was taking up too much time
So the first task was excluded
I used the rate limiter task
the lru cache task
And the recursive fibonacci task
Um
One malvalidator rate limiter
Recursively bonacci
Yeah, while you guys look that over I
gotta I gotta let my dogs out really quick
Yeah
Oh
And then um
I also have a different teammate who's been running some
tasks with a red agent turned
on.
So he's been like putting in custom scenarios.
And he shared a database file with me earlier today.
I haven't looked over this, this file.
I'll put it inside the repository and
just give it a label that it's his database.
So this is a Python file.
Josh.
Yeah.
Looks a description.
So where is the database file?
Is this being used to create a database of all the tasks?
Is how I understand.
It's complicated, but where you can
find the database is in, let me see.
Hold on.
I got to get to the right branch here.
My teammate wanted all the databases deleted from master,
but they're still existing in
my working branch here.
I think it's in the data folder.
Here we go.
Okay.
Yeah.
Let me show you this specific link so
that you guys will be in the right branch.
Thank you.
My most recent changes were pushed
to this branch early this morning.
In data.
Okay, great.
Yeah.
Okay.
I'm seeing a database.
What kind of database is this?
Is it a?
I think it should be SQLite.
SQLite, yes.
Okay.
Let me verify that.
I mean, that's been the goal.
So hopefully it stayed that, but I don't know.
I've been doing a lot of work.
Okay.
So all the tasks are in the database or
are all the results from the agents logged in
the databases.
There are a few databases here.
So the database, the databases
contain logs from Browns that were run.
So.
Okay.
So it should hopefully contain information
about each task that was run, how the task
was validated, the results of each scoring, and then the
weights of the scoring and then
the final combined score.
Right.
Okay.
Because the green agent, it rates
it using four different metrics.
There's three quantifiable ones,
the contextual integrity score.
So architectural testing and rationale.
A good acronym to remember is RAT.
So R for rationale, A for
architectural, and T for testing, RAT.
So the RAT scores, those are all quantifiable.
And then the logic score is ironically
an agent as a judge, an LLM as a judge.
So that score is finally
whatever LLM is loaded into the arena.
It's prompted to review the
outputted code and provide a score.
Is that the green agent?
Yeah.
That's the green agent.
For these tests, I turned the red agent off.
Oh, because.
Because I just purely wanted to test
what we're trying to argue for in the paper.
Right now, I haven't.
Okay.
Yeah.
Because we are only submitting today for the.
We need to not submit tomorrow.
Is that right?
Is that the reason?
Yeah.
But the thing is, if I can clean up, if I
can clean up the repository enough, I will
leave in the red agent as an option.
Okay.
And I will be running more arena tests today.
But yesterday, what I wanted to do is I just wanted to
create a really simple set of test
results.
Right.
For us to analyze that, just focus on the contextual
integrity score and just keep the
red agent turned off so that we can
kind of just stay focused on the paper.
Because it's like, we need proof that what
we're arguing for in the paper has value.
And I'm hoping that these sets of
battles will provide that proof.
So let me start creating that briefing
document that will provide the file paths.
Because there's a lot of database files in that folder.
And you'll need the three correct ones.
And then one of them has the scores weighted differently.
And we'll have to disclose that
in the briefing document for today.
Okay.
So, yeah, basically what should be proven here in this
theory is like, even though the
green agent is run by an LLM, is
the same LLM as the purple agent.
Like let's say, you know, like, like
Mistral, a really tiny agent versus Quinn, a larger
agent and then GPT OSS 20B.
Theoretically, the contextual integrity scores should be
higher, the better the agent is
at coding, even if the agent is grading itself.
And then there, you know, it can get deeper than that.
There's, there's more things I was trying to prove, but
like, that's, that's basically
like the simplest conclusion
that I wanted to draw from that.
I'll be honest, I spent a lot of time
setting this up and debugging the past 48 hours.
So I'm kind of, yeah, I'm kind of scatterbrained right now.
So it would, it would kind of help if you guys have like
any other questions, but because
like I'll have to spend, I'll have to spend time providing
the answers to these questions
today.
No problems.
Yeah.
So I won't ask many questions.
My main questions are, so are you submitting this whole
repo in the competition today,
or just the green agent part of the repo?
And then the second is, are we, I think you said we were
supposed to record a video or
something.
Oh, because it is due today at 12 o'clock PST.
Oh boy.
So instead of being, let me see.
Oh, great.
Oh, instead of the 16th, it's the 15th.
Okay.
That's, that's fine.
Yeah.
I will have to produce the video today.
I thought we had an extra day.
No, we today and you know what will happen?
Josh is many people will try to submit at
the last minute and the network will, I'm
sure there are a lot of people.
So and then the third question is, so we, so you will
create the video because you have
an expertise in all that work of camera and everything.
Yeah.
And I don't think I'm going to show my face in the video.
I think I'm, what I'm basically going to do is create a
PowerPoint slide that, you know,
shows some good visualizations.
I'll probably show some code snippets.
Right.
And then hopefully if you're able to visualize the results
of the tests that I ran yesterday,
I'll show some visualizations of that.
And then we can also include that in the paper.
And then, and then we'll just have to submit what we have.
So okay.
I thought we were going to have an extra 24 hours here.
So where this, this is going to be, we're going to be
cutting it close today, for sure.
Right.
And then that is fine.
I think you have done all the
work on arranging it together.
So now, so we are only submitting for the green agent.
You would be able to create the video without your picture
and then include a house, whoever
you want.
If you want any help, let me know.
And then the third question is, since we are only
submitting for the green agent, when
was the, when is the due date for the lambda track?
I forgot, but we can check.
From what I understand, it says the 16th in that.
Okay.
But lambda.
Yeah, I'm second guessing myself now
because I thought it was the 16th for.
No, it is.
They keep sending emails.
It is today and then it is today at 12 p.m.
At 12 o'clock midnight.
Okay.
Well, lambdas document says November 24th to January 16th.
So that could mean, I mean, they
don't provide a, what time zone.
I'm going to assume it's the same
exact time as our competition here.
It says, I didn't share with you.
It says, remember that agent beats
phase one submission deadline is tomorrow.
It I received it yesterday.
Make sure to submit your
projects by January 15th, 11.59 p.m.
Pacific time.
Okay.
So now my third question is.
What I opened here.
Yeah.
Now the diagram that we produced
and then you updated it to meet.
Yeah.
Is I put it here.
This diagram, this shows lambda
track and also the custom track.
I shared it in the meeting.
Comment messages here.
Let me take a look.
Yeah.
So now how will this document apply to what we are
submitting if you're only submitting
the green agent.
Do you want me to produce one just for the green agent?
That would be awesome if you could.
Okay.
Yeah.
Then updated this.
Do we have a copy a document for
the green agent now in the docs?
You mean like a high level overview of the current
functionality of the green agent?
Yeah.
Because now we are only submitting the green agent, right?
Submitting the lambda track right now.
This is tough for me to answer because technically my
teammate did a lot of work on using the
red agent and kind of incorporating it into the green agent
and he's running pretty successful
tests.
The test that I ran yesterday, I had that turned off
because he was working on it.
So it's tough because it would be valuable if we...
You know what?
I would just say for this track, for the custom green agent
track, let's just submit it without
the red agent.
What I'll do is I'll create a branch
in the repository where it's removed.
And I'll clean up the documentation so that only essential
documents exist and make sure
that there's no junk files because there's a few.
And then...
Okay.
Yeah.
And then once that finishes,
you know, we'll see how it goes.
But yeah, I'm planning on only submitting the green agent.
I mean, I kept it turned off, but
I kept the red agent turned off.
And the purple agent?
The purple agent?
Yeah, of course.
Of course I'll be including that because
that's required as part of the submission.
Yes.
Okay. And I'll provide documentation
for how that functions as well.
But yeah.
Oh man, this is a lot.
Okay.
So lambda drag what red agent submission?
I'm checking the red line.
Red agent.
Green agent.
Tomorrow is a judging.
Okay.
And then purple agent is February 2.
Phase 1 is just the green agent.
The purple agent is February 2.
And then the red agent.
It's yet to be announced.
Lambda drag, right?
Yeah, it's yet to be announced because they will be for
phase 2, they'll be selecting
the green agents from phase 1.
Okay.
So okay, then I think we got a bit of work to do.
If you can pull a branch with only the red agent related to
green agent related information,
right?
And then let me know.
And then if there is a document just for the green agent,
then I focus on building this
pictorial just for the green agent.
What do you think, Allah?
Is that good?
Yeah, I mean, it sounds like
you have things sorted outside.
I don't want to be disruptive, but if I
can help speed anything up, let me know.
Okay.
Yeah.
No problem.
I may need help with publishing on archive.
I've never done that before.
So I'll need to make sure that
I have the formatting correct.
Yeah.
If you could send me the complete paper,
then I'll have to turn into latex and then
PDF, then we can put it here.
Yeah.
So is it okay if I just give you a plain markdown file?
Would that be possible?
Yeah.
Okay.
I'll do the rest myself.
So okay.
Thank you.
Yeah.
If you can handle that, that would be absolutely perfect.
Mm hmm.
And then, um, yeah, deep tea.
I'm going to send you, I'm first going to send you the, the
briefing document that provides
links to all of the database, the three database files that
you need and explains how the scoring
was weighted differently in one of them.
And I'll try and repair that.
If I can't repair that.
So you can just visualize like the individual pillars of
the scoring instead of the final
weighted score.
Cause like two of the, two of the database documents were
created with a equal 25% weight
between all four parts of the score.
You know, the rat score 25% per each of that.
And then 25% for the logic score.
But one of them is 20, 20, 20, 40.
The logic score got a 40% weight.
So I want to fix that.
I think the information, there's enough information in the
database to fix that because it's just
a final score weight.
But if I, for some reason cannot do
that, we'll have to work around that.
Okay.
It should be pretty simple.
And then I can get you the information for
what exactly was done to like what battles
were ran.
I can give you like names of specific
models if you want in the briefing document.
I will continue to update the briefing document too.
So in the same working branch.
Okay.
So once you update, then let me know and then I'll add the
pictorial there with the link
to the dogs, right?
Is that good?
Yeah.
Okay.
And then by, I will be out from 6 30 to 9 Eastern time.
So I can do before that or after that.
If you are able to do it by three, which is by into a
before 330 your time, then I can
update before or I'll do afterwards.
That good.
Yeah.
Let me know on Slack.
Okay.
Around 3pm Pacific time.
Yes.
Before you will be cutting close because I
have to leave at 330 Pacific, but I'll be
back.
I can do later today or I can, if you have time now,
whichever way we can just play
by the discord messages, right?
I'll keep checking.
Yeah.
Okay.
Yeah, that works great.
Yeah.
And then the time to submit is 11 59pm.
So as I said, usually it becomes
very hard to submit towards the end.
So let's target submitting by like 11pm
PST and maybe have a dry run before that.
I don't know if you want to.
I'll aim for 10 so that we have an extra.
Yeah.
I'll try and have everything in
order by 10pm, including the video.
I'm probably not going to focus too much on the video.
I'm probably just going to make sure that there's enough
for them to be satisfied, but
I'm not going to go overboard since we
only have a few hours to complete it.
Yes.
Okay.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Right.
Okay.
Yeah.
I recorded this meeting.
I'm going to.
Yeah.
I'm going to save the transcript of this
meeting and then I'm going to use it to copy
the briefing document that
contains all the information that we need.
And that document will be ready
within like the next hour or so.
Okay.
I also shared the link for the Overleaf project where I'll
be creating the Latex document.
So in case you want to make any last minute changes after I
convert everything, then yeah,
you could do that.
Yeah.
Thank you so much.
No worries.
If you also want to hang on
the educator quickly, it's fine.
Yeah.
Oh, not register.
Oh, I have to register.
Let me see. Let me see.
And then I saw one of your messages,
Josh, about lambda track registration.
I don't know.
I couldn't find that message again on Slack.
Was it sent?
Usually it is a new message that box up.
So it's in.
So let me show you here.
So Discord's kind of funny.
Where the direct messages are stored.
They're actually stored where this logo is in the top left.
Can you see my screen that I'm sharing?
Yeah.
So if you just click here and then you find my name here.
Oh, let me see.
Direct messages.
Oh, oh yeah.
I found it now.
Why couldn't find it?
Well, it's okay.
Because if you didn't sign up the team.
I thought you signed up the team a couple of months ago for
the lambda track after a meeting.
But it's okay if you did.
It's okay if you did not.
I can take care of that today.
I just needed to know whether you did or not.
No, I didn't do the registration.
We were discussing about whether
to use lambda and the other track.
So if you want me to register, I can do that.
Or otherwise you can do it.
Whichever way is fine.
Okay.
That's fine.
Yeah, I'm just going to do that.
Let me see if I can find it.
Yeah.
Don't worry about it.
I'll make sure that's added to the team
briefing document too as an action item.
Okay.
I have to sign up.
I have to team sign up.
Okay, no worries.
Yeah, I think we covered everything.
Yeah.
It's kind of a lot to do today.
I also got to call my mom check in with
her because I haven't heard from her yet.
I got to make sure she's doing well too.
But yeah, I will continue to give
you guys updates throughout today.
And the first thing I'll create is that briefing document.
Okay, great.
Cool.
Yeah.
So I'll start converting the copyright research paper as
well and just start putting it there
and then whatever small changes
we need to make later we can make.
Yeah.
Oh, sweet.
Using the Overleaf website?
Yeah, yeah.
The same project link that I shared with you.
I think this way you could save time, right?
I started working.
Yeah.
Absolutely.
Well, thank you so much for attending, guys.
I really appreciate it.
Thank you for meeting with me.
You guys are being a great help right now because I would
not be ready for a submission
without you guys.
So I really, really appreciate it.
Yeah, thank you.
Thank you.
We got this.
Right, guys?
Yeah.
We'll be done soon.
Just we'll keep checking this card also.
Okay.
Yeah.
I got you.
Thanks.
Have a good one, guys.
Bye-bye.
Thank you.